<Cars>
<Car>
          <ID>1</ID>
          <Name>Vauxhall</Name>
          <Model>Astra GTC</Model>
          <FullModel>1.4T SRi Coupe 3dr Petrol Manual Euro 5 (s/s) (140 ps)</FullModel>
          <EyeCatcher>Full MOT | Serviced | Warranty</EyeCatcher>
          <Description>
              At AW Trade Centre, we pride ourselves on delivering superb customer service and offering a wide selection of quality used cars. Whether you&apos;re searching for a reliable daily driver or a unique find, we make it easy to discover the perfect vehicle to suit your needs.
              - Every car comes with the care, expertise, and attention to detail that have become the hallmark of AW Trade Centre. Our friendly team is here to guide you through every step of the journey — from browsing to driving away making your car-buying experience smooth and enjoyable.
              - Let us help you find a car you’ll love, at a price you can feel good about.
              - Buy with confidence: all our cars are fully inspected, test-driven, and serviced. Plus, every vehicle comes with a comprehensive warranty for your peace of mind. (Please note: our process for part exchanges differs—get in touch for more information).
              - 
              - This hatchback offers a balance of performance, efficiency, and technology. Powered by a 1.4L 4-cylinder turbo charged engine, it delivers approximately 140 horsepower and is paired with 6-speed manual transmision.
              - Inside, the vehicle features a spacious cabin with seating for five, half leather upholstery, and a user-friendly infotainment system, with the option to spec the car with an upgraded infotainment screen, which includes apple car play and android auto. Additional tech includes Bluetooth connectivity, USB ports, voice command functionality, contact for more information.
              - 
              - Technical data:
              - Fuel efficiency ranges from 47.1 MPG combined as stated by the manufacturers. Cargo space is generous, with rear seats that fold down to expand storage capacity.
          </Description>
          <Value>2699</Value>
          <Mileage>98800</Mileage>
          <YearOfManu>2013</YearOfManu>
          <CatStat>Clear</CatStat>
          <FuelType>Petrol</FuelType>
          <Transmission>Manual</Transmission>
          <Colour>Black</Colour>
          <ExtraFeatures></ExtraFeatures>
          <Reg>DK13 RUH</Reg>
          <Image>https://i.imgur.com/qxCHECj.jpeg, https://i.imgur.com/sEQy76o.png, https://i.imgur.com/6pwBGFC.png, https://i.imgur.com/QL8LYKD.png, https://i.imgur.com/d7SZ54u.png, https://i.imgur.com/LBmRbB3.png, https://i.imgur.com/JrKVFkf.jpeg, https://i.imgur.com/5vTFik5.jpeg, https://i.imgur.com/RhYrxKX.jpeg, https://i.imgur.com/fxVLPmv.jpeg, https://i.imgur.com/wQnOvYA.jpeg, https://i.imgur.com/sCDpI6K.jpeg, https://i.imgur.com/gLWARK0.jpeg, https://i.imgur.com/F7qLANQ.jpeg, https://i.imgur.com/jWQl6zY.jpeg, https://i.imgur.com/sZR8htN.jpeg, https://i.imgur.com/3Pw9O1P.jpeg, https://i.imgur.com/OnS1krP.jpeg, https://i.imgur.com/qLGkFEK.jpeg, https://i.imgur.com/LkLU9jG.jpeg, https://i.imgur.com/j0cyp2h.jpeg, https://i.imgur.com/UiTfRb8.jpeg, https://i.imgur.com/ccIUfvR.jpeg, https://i.imgur.com/unIJGoI.jpeg, https://i.imgur.com/L9erHtp.jpeg, https://i.imgur.com/CwiA7yP.jpeg, https://i.imgur.com/3duQa8T.jpeg, https://i.imgur.com/oDl2epi.jpeg, https://i.imgur.com/Nb2Egsu.jpeg, https://i.imgur.com/1HNGrEF.jpeg, https://i.imgur.com/2kvvQpO.jpeg, https://i.imgur.com/Rjw7LT8.jpeg, https://i.imgur.com/fGflnyo.jpeg</Image>
          <Video></Video>
          <MetaTag>2013 Vauxhall Astra GTC for Sale Northeast, best prices at Aw trade centre, located in Billingham, North Yorkshire.</MetaTag>
</Car>
<Car>
          <ID>2</ID>
          <Name>Ford</Name>
          <Model>Focus Zetec </Model>
          <FullModel>1.6 TDCi Zetec Hatchback 5dr Diesel Manual Euro 5 (s/s) (115 ps)</FullModel>
          <EyeCatcher>Serviced | Warranty | Nationwide Delivery</EyeCatcher>
          <Description>
              At AW Trade Centre, we pride ourselves on delivering superb customer service and offering a wide selection of quality used cars. Whether you&apos;re searching for a reliable daily driver or a unique find, we make it easy to discover the perfect vehicle to suit your needs.
              - Every car comes with the care, expertise, and attention to detail that have become the hallmark of AW Trade Centre. Our friendly team is here to guide you through every step of the journey — from browsing to driving away making your car-buying experience smooth and enjoyable.
              - Let us help you find a car you’ll love, at a price you can feel good about.
              - Buy with confidence: all our cars are fully inspected, test-driven, and serviced. Plus, every vehicle comes with a comprehensive warranty for your peace of mind. (Please note: our process for part exchanges differs—get in touch for more information).
              - 
              - This hatchback offers a balance of performance, efficiency, and technology. Powered by a 1.6L 4-cylinder turbo charged engine, it delivers approximately 113 horsepower and is paired with 6-speed manual transmision.
              - Inside, the vehicle features a spacious cabin with seating for five, cloth upholstery, and a user-friendly infotainment system, with the option to spec the car with an upgraded infotainment screen, which includes apple car play and android auto. Additional tech includes Bluetooth connectivity, USB ports, voice command functionality, contact for more information.
              - 
              - Technical data:
              - Fuel efficiency ranges from 67.3 mpg combined as stated by the manufacturers. Cargo space is generous, with rear seats that fold down to expand storage capacity.
              - 
          </Description>
          <Value>3299</Value>
          <Mileage>89500</Mileage>
          <YearOfManu>2012</YearOfManu>
          <CatStat>Clear</CatStat>
          <FuelType>Diesel</FuelType>
          <Transmission>Manual</Transmission>
          <Colour>Grey</Colour>
          <ExtraFeatures>16in Alloy Wheels - 5x2 Spoke, Air Conditioning, Bluetooth Handsfree and Voice Control, Bright Finish on Upper Door Line, Centre Console with open Stowage Bins, Chrome Finish on Upper Door Line, Door Mirrors - Heated - Electric - Integrated Side Indicators - Body Coloured, EBD - Electronic Brakeforce Distribution, ESP - Electronic Stability Programme, Emergency Brake Lights, Ford DAB Audio System, Ford Easy-Fuel Capless Refuelling System, Ford SYNC, Front Fog Lights, Front suspension - Independent with MacPherson Struts, IPS - Intelligent Protection System, Pollen Filter, Rear Spoiler, Seats - 60-40 Rear Split Back, Seats - Front Sports, TVC - Torque Vectoring Control, Thatcham Category 1 Alarm, Traction Control - TC, USB Connection - iPod Connectivity, Voice Control - Audio</ExtraFeatures>
          <Reg>HV62 FYL</Reg>
          <Image>https://i.imgur.com/5o90Tky.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/u2jjJmF.png,https://i.imgur.com/2rTZgE1.png,https://i.imgur.com/7LyKK93.png,https://i.imgur.com/VSUa64d.png,https://i.imgur.com/RZcGFAr.png,https://i.imgur.com/seDuXcS.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/lQhXpaI.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/WWPP6Dy.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/j53LdRO.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/gQfhC2K.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/fF0Q3DB.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/dkXyggF.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/kVsW35t.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/VqEQHNZ.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/tTSQtay.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/d7W96Me.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/mi4R4hz.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/JLOod9R.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/aaBgV8B.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/80M6v3R.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/rkzfaSt.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/LdCbAP5.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/P21F5Gj.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/8ifgFnu.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/TWYKX5k.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/FAlBw0P.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/RkTfgHr.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/CFg7gHA.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/rhkF3ja.jpeg</Image>
          <Video></Video>
          <MetaTag>2012 Ford Focus Zetec, £20 12 months road tax, for Sale Northeast, best prices at Aw trade centre, located in Billingham, North Yorkshire</MetaTag>
</Car>

          
<Car>
          <ID>3</ID>
          <Name>Mitsubishi</Name>
          <Model>ASX 3 </Model>
          <FullModel>1.6 3 SUV 5dr Petrol Manual Euro 5 (117 ps)</FullModel>
          <EyeCatcher>SERVICED | WARRANTY | DELIVERY</EyeCatcher>
          <Description>
              At AW Trade Centre, we pride ourselves on delivering superb customer service and offering a wide selection of quality used cars. Whether you&apos;re searching for a reliable daily driver or a unique find, we make it easy to discover the perfect vehicle to suit your needs.
              - 
              - Every car comes with the care, expertise, and attention to detail that have become the hallmark of AW Trade Centre. Our friendly team is here to guide you through every step of the journey  from browsing to driving away making your car buying experience smooth and enjoyable. Let us help you find a car you&apos;ll love, at a price you can feel good about.
              - 
              - Buy with confidence: all our cars are fully inspected, test driven, and serviced. Plus, every vehicle comes with a comprehensive warranty for your peace of mind. (Please note: our process for part exchanges differsget in touch for more information).
              - 
              - This SUV offers a balance of performance, efficiency, and technology. Powered by a 1.6L 4 cylinder turbo charged engine, it delivers approximately 115 horsepower and is paired with a 5 speed manual transmission.
              - 
              - Inside, the vehicle features a spacious cabin with seating for five, cloth upholstery, and a user friendly infotainment system, with the option to spec the car with an upgraded infotainment screen, which includes apple car play and android auto. Additional tech includes Bluetooth connectivity, USB ports, voice command functionality, contact for more information. The vehicle also features heated seats, cruise control, and alloy wheels.
              - 
              - Technical data:
              - 
              - Fuel efficiency ranges from 47.9 mpg combined as stated by the manufacturers. Cargo space is generous, with rear seats that fold down to expand storage capacity. The vehicle is also ULEZ compliant.
              - 
              - Vehicle registered: 13/08/2013
          </Description>
          <Value>3499</Value>
          <Mileage>85200</Mileage>
          <YearOfManu>2013</YearOfManu>
          <CatStat>Clear</CatStat>
          <FuelType>Petrol</FuelType>
          <Transmission>Manual</Transmission>
          <Colour>Grey</Colour>
          <ExtraFeatures>17in Alloy Wheels, ASC - Active Stability Control, Air Conditioning - Climate Control, Air Filter, Airbags - Front Passenger Deactivation Switch, Alarm, Armrest - Front and Rear Doors - Fabric, Armrest - Rear Centre with Cup Holders and Load Through Hatch, Belt Line Moulding - Chrome, Bluetooth Hands Free Telephone Connection, Brake Over Ride System, Bumpers - Lower Front and Rear and Side Sills - Black, Central Door Locking - Keyless Entry, Coat Hanger, Cruise Control, Door Handles - Body Colour, Door Handles - Interior - Chrome, Door Mirrors - Electrically Adjustable-Heated-Folding, Door Sashes - Black, EBD - Electronic Brakeforce Distribution, Engine Start-Stop Button, Exhaust Finisher - Chrome, Footrest - Drivers, Front Fog Lights - with Chrome Bezels, Gear Knob - Leather Wrapped - Black, Glovebox - Illuminated, Head Restraints - Height Adjustable Front x2, Head Restraints - Height Adjustable Rear x3, Headlights - Automatic Light Sensor, Headlights - Halogen, Headlights - Levelling Adjustment, Instrument Meter Trim - Chrome, Instrument Panel Dimmer, Interior Light - Front, Interior Light - Rear, Keyless Operation System, Luggage Area Light, Map Reading Lights - Front, Multi Information Display - Colour, Parking Sensors - Rear, Privacy Glass, RISE - Reinforced Impact Safety Evolution - Body Safety System, Rear Seat Heater Ducts, Seatbelt Fastening Warning Light, Seatbelts - 3-Point ELR x 2 with Force Limiters and Pretensioners - Front, Seats - 60-40 Split Rear Folding Backrests, Seats - Front Slide and Recline Adjustment, Seats - Rear Backrest Adjustment, Speakers x6, Spoiler - Roof Body Colour, Sunvisors x2, TCL - Traction Control, USB Connection, Window Demister with Timer - Rear, Wipers - Intermittent with Washer - Rear, Wipers - Variable Intermittent with Washer -</ExtraFeatures>
          <Reg>SM13 RWO</Reg>
          <Image>https://i.imgur.com/dB82Fzu.png,https://i.imgur.com/rqK9qQs.png,https://i.imgur.com/qG7Ouk7.png,https://i.imgur.com/IY77Pv1.png,https://i.imgur.com/AC9jnQe.png,https://i.imgur.com/Ky2tCkF.png,https://i.imgur.com/9DenpLk.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/VgbDA0B.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/hbo2Rfp.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/KyjGNhZ.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/hTubcFU.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/7GL9ejo.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/Oz45hUB.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/mY5tnjk.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/e2k1s93.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/3gONMSD.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/YDKN1Vz.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/ckIooLY.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/S5Qf9oW.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/HllCKGe.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/Xw6HmO2.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/cLVWj3j.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/ZBEBJEw.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/VgDTwYq.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/jyx9V8e.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/AVMDOJJ.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/E0odzDD.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/9Z1WueB.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/ifAr4rj.jpeg</Image>
          <Video></Video>
          <MetaTag></MetaTag>
</Car>

          <Car>
          <ID>4</ID>
          <Name>SEAT</Name>
          <Model>Ibiza Sport</Model>
          <FullModel>1.4 16V Sport Sport Coupe 3dr Petrol Manual Euro 4 (85 ps)</FullModel>
          <EyeCatcher>Serviced | 3 Owners | Nationwide Delivery</EyeCatcher>
          <Description>
              At AW Trade Centre, we pride ourselves on delivering superb customer service and offering a wide selection of quality used cars. Whether you&apos;re searching for a reliable daily driver or a unique find, we make it easy to discover the perfect vehicle to suit your needs.
              - Every car comes with the care, expertise, and attention to detail that have become the hallmark of AW Trade Centre. Our friendly team is here to guide you through every step of the journey — from browsing to driving away making your car-buying experience smooth and enjoyable.
              - Let us help you find a car you’ll love, at a price you can feel good about.
              - Buy with confidence: all our cars are fully inspected, test-driven, and serviced. Plus, every vehicle comes with a comprehensive warranty for your peace of mind. (Please note: our process for part exchanges differs—get in touch for more information).
              - 
              - This hatchback offers a balance of performance, efficiency, and technology. Powered by a 1.4L 4-cylinder engine, it delivers approximately 86 horsepower and is paired with 5-speed manual transmision.
              - Inside, the vehicle features a spacious cabin with seating for five, cloth upholstery, and a user-friendly infotainment system, with the option to spec the car with an upgraded infotainment screen, which includes apple car play and android auto. contact for more information.
              - 
              - Technical data:
              - Fuel efficiency ranges from 45.6 mpg combined as stated by the manufacturers. Cargo space is generous, with rear seats that fold down to expand storage capacity.
              - 
          </Description>
          <Value>1899</Value>
          <Mileage>110000</Mileage>
          <YearOfManu>2009</YearOfManu>
          <CatStat>Clear</CatStat>
          <FuelType>Petrol</FuelType>
          <Transmission>Manual</Transmission>
          <Colour>Red</Colour>
          <ExtraFeatures></ExtraFeatures>
          <Reg>CX59 UBT</Reg>
          <Image>https://i.imgur.com/bJWsZ6v.png,https://i.imgur.com/0tbhKqL.png,https://i.imgur.com/bBHbeMB.png,https://i.imgur.com/Wqs7KQ7.png,https://i.imgur.com/55RY39z.png,https://i.imgur.com/e7AnVKS.png,https://i.imgur.com/icj958x.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/u7c5455.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/92ZjaHN.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/gX36AIt.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/BF8YZ2l.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/aBkhjwU.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/vw8dHQA.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/S5M1tYu.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/MrPoZ5j.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/kuZ15At.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/1LakGcm.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/49dTVrN.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/Ij4XvhN.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/fiaObIM.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/Pu6uTp2.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/ooBkDZ1.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/30Wyjec.jpeg</Image>
          <Video></Video>
          <MetaTag></MetaTag>
</Car>

          <Car>
          <ID>5</ID>
          <Name>Audi</Name>
          <Model>A4 Avant Black Edition</Model>
          <FullModel>2.0 TDI Black Edition Estate 5dr Diesel Manual Euro 5 (s/s) (177 ps)</FullModel>
          <EyeCatcher>Serviced | Ice Cold AC | Panroof</EyeCatcher>
          <Description>
              At AW Trade Centre, we pride ourselves on delivering superb customer service and offering a wide selection of quality used cars. Whether you&apos;re searching for a reliable daily driver or a unique find, we make it easy to discover the perfect vehicle to suit your needs.
              - Every car comes with the care, expertise, and attention to detail that have become the hallmark of AW Trade Centre. Our friendly team is here to guide you through every step of the journey — from browsing to driving away making your car-buying experience smooth and enjoyable.
              - Let us help you find a car you’ll love, at a price you can feel good about.
              - Buy with confidence: all our cars are fully inspected, test-driven, and serviced. Plus, every vehicle comes with a comprehensive warranty for your peace of mind. (Please note: our process for part exchanges differs—get in touch for more information).
              - 
              - This Estate offers a balance of performance, efficiency, and technology. Powered by a 2.0L 4-cylinder engine, it delivers approximately 174 horsepower and is paired with 6-speed manual transmission.
              - Inside, the vehicle features a spacious cabin with seating for five, half leather upholstery, and a user-friendly infotainment system, with the option to spec the car with an upgraded infotainment screen, which includes apple car play and android auto, some of the tech include Bluetooth, electric hand brake, front and rear sensors, electric boot. contact for more information.
              - 
              - Technical data:
              - Fuel efficiency ranges from 58.9 mpg combined as stated by the manufacturers. Cargo space is generous, with rear seats that fold down to expand storage capacity.
          </Description>
          <Value>6750</Value>
          <Mileage>140000</Mileage>
          <YearOfManu>2015</YearOfManu>
          <CatStat>Cat N</CatStat>
          <FuelType>Diesel</FuelType>
          <Transmission>Manual</Transmission>
          <Colour>Blue</Colour>
          <ExtraFeatures></ExtraFeatures>
          <Reg>YY15 GYZ</Reg>
          <Image>https://i.imgur.com/KWocV90.png,https://i.imgur.com/Iy4m8Km.png,https://i.imgur.com/bcCvJNs.png,https://i.imgur.com/IyEMIyq.png,https://i.imgur.com/8rt2R9X.png,https://i.imgur.com/282YhH9.png,https://i.imgur.com/JRT3VqK.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/hhMpc5R.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/OZYawU5.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/4Cdp9ad.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/lpoBEUP.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/owNCZ2C.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/tewFHHa.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/wtskNoe.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/UTP3P6v.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/UzKrQ0g.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/efgGgLg.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/jv6HuWl.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/DVuNBxT.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/djHmAmg.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/wDSsckF.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/javCnh6.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/tRBfOFk.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/RyyghVj.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/QliWG68.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/TGljYMo.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/j0DuvYa.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/roX822p.jpeg,https://i.imgur.com/OHlhvDK.jpeg</Image>
          <Video></Video>
          <MetaTag></MetaTag>
</Car>
</Cars>
