<Cars>
  <Car>
    <ID>1</ID>
    <Name>Audi</Name>
    <Model>Q3</Model>
    <FullModel>2.0 TDI S line Plus S Tronic quattro Euro 5 (s/s) 5dr</FullModel>
    <EyeCatcher>T-BELT KIT✅WARRANTY✅AUTO✅4X4✅</EyeCatcher>
    <Value>6499</Value>
    <Mileage>128900</Mileage>
    <YearOfManu>2014</YearOfManu>
    <CatStat>Clear</CatStat>
    <FuelType>Diesel</FuelType>
    <Transmission>Automatic</Transmission>
    <Colour>Black</Colour>
    <ExtraFeatures></ExtraFeatures>
    <Reg>NA14VNF</Reg>
    <Video></Video>
    <MetaTag></MetaTag>
    <Tax>265</Tax>
    <Insurance>24E</Insurance>
    <Mpg>47.9</Mpg>
    <AT>autotrader.co.uk/car-details/202601159171692?journey=DEALER_STOCK_LIST_JOURNEY&amp;sort=price-asc&amp;twcs=true&amp;searchId=48062c9d-4888-4e50-b468-8b66864f70a7&amp;advertising-location=at_profile_cars&amp;advertising-location=at_cars&amp;page=1&amp;postcode=ts55ex&amp;fromsra&amp;fromDealerSearchResults&amp;backLinkQueryParams=advertising-location%3Dat_cars%26advertising-location%3Dat_profile_cars%26onesearchad%3DUsed%26onesearchad%3DNearly%2520New%26onesearchad%3DNew%26postcode%3Dts55ex%26retailerId%3D10041187%26sort%3Dprice-asc%26flrfc%3D1</AT>
    <Description>
      - Available now is this stunning and well-maintained 2014 Audi Q3 2.0 TDI S line Plus S tronic quattro, a premium compact SUV offering strong performance, luxury comfort, and excellent all-weather capability.
      - Powered by the 2.0 TDI diesel engine paired with the smooth S tronic automatic gearbox and quattro four-wheel drive, it delivers confident handling, impressive fuel economy, and the refined driving experience Audi is known for.
      - ✅ S line Plus • S tronic Auto • quattro 4WD
      - Key Features Include:
      - • S line Plus styling and interior
      - • S tronic automatic transmission
      - • quattro four-wheel drive
      - • Half-leather / Alcantara S line sport seats
      - • Satellite navigation system
      - • Bluetooth and media connectivity
      - • Dual-zone climate control
      - • Cruise control
      - • Xenon headlights with LED daytime running lights
      - • Front and rear parking sensors
      - • Multifunction steering wheel
      - • Alloy wheels
      - • Electric windows and mirrors
      - • ISOFIX
      - Drives superb — smooth, powerful, and extremely refined. No warning lights or mechanical issues.
      - • Recently serviced and inspected
      - • MOT expires October 2026
      - ✅ Drive away today – reserve NA14 VNF with a refundable £100 deposit (TandCs apply).
      - 🚚 Nationwide delivery available at competitive rates.
      - ⸻
      - Why Buy from AW Trade Centre?
      - We provide:
      - • Full mechanical inspection
      - • Free comprehensive warranty
      - • HPI clear vehicles (unless otherwise stated)
      - • Fresh valet inside and out
      - • Friendly, honest, and pressure-free service
      - 📞 Call or message us today to arrange a viewing or reserve this Audi Q3 S line Plus quattro Auto
    </Description>
    <Image>https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w800/6a8f5f58d11940ad9cbbd53b1d092ff7.jpg,
https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w600/0cee92512e554821a1c110ef4ebab98d.jpg,
https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w600/b1d87cdcd775423cb09a8afb07ac9578.jpg,
https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w600/a1ff1e385521424a8b020b478fe61768.jpg,
https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w600/07f4f42bb50240cb838b6407bb789bad.jpg,
https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w600/2bc03faa411b4aaba376a44b43376188.jpg,
https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w600/04ec65334b31485da9469028a0e550a7.jpg</Image>
  </Car>
  <Car>
    <ID>2</ID>
    <Name>Audi</Name>
    <Model>A5</Model>
    <FullModel>2.0 TFSI S line S Tronic Euro 6 (s/s) 2dr</FullModel>
    <EyeCatcher>SERVICED✅12M WARRANTY✅DELIVERY</EyeCatcher>
    <Value>10799</Value>
    <Mileage>74000</Mileage>
    <YearOfManu>2018</YearOfManu>
    <CatStat>CAT S</CatStat>
    <FuelType>Petrol</FuelType>
    <Transmission>Automatic</Transmission>
    <Colour>Black</Colour>
    <ExtraFeatures>2 x USB Charging Ports and 1 x AUX-IN, Audi Connect Infotainment Services - 3 Month Trial, Audi Connect Safety and Service, Audi Smartphone Interface, Audi Sound System, Bluetooth Interface, CD Drive, DAB Digital Radio Reception, MMI Navigation - SD Card Based, Tow Bar Preparation, Audi Drive Select, Colour Drivers Information System with 7in High-Resolution TFT Screen, Cruise Control with Speed Limiter, Tyre Pressure Warning Light, Voice Control System, 18in Alloy Wheels - 5-Twin-Spoke Star Design, 19in Alloy Wheels - Multi-Spoke Design - Contrasting Grey - Partly Polished, Air Inlets - Horizontal Inlay in Matt Aluminium, Anti Theft Locking Wheel Bolts, Black exterior colour, Body Coloured Door Mirrors, Door Mirrors - Electrically Adjustable and Heated with Built-in LED Indicators, Door Mirrors - Folding, Dual-Branch Design with 1 Exhaust Tailpipe on the Left and Right, Electric Windows - Front, High Gloss Package, Honeycomb Side Air Inlet Grille in Titan Black, Radiator Grille in Twilight Grey with Matt Aluminium Inlays, Rear Diffuser in Twilight Grey Matt with Honeycomb Grille, Rear Grille - Black Grained, S Line Badges on Front Wings, S Line Front and Rear Bumpers, S line Side Skirts in Black, Space Saver Spare Wheel, Windscreen with Acoustic Glazing, LED Headlights with LED Rear Lights and Dynamic Rear Indicators, Light and Rain Sensor, 4-Way Electric Lumbar Support, Auto-Dimming Rear-View Mirror, Cloth Headlining in Black, Contrast Stitching on Seats - Steering Wheel and Gear Lever Gaiter, Deluxe 3-Zone Electronic Climate Control, Electric Boot Lid Release, Electrically Adjustable Front Seats, Email - Calendar and Text Messages can be Displayed on your Vehicles MMI, Front Centre Armrest, Front and Rear Floor Mats, Gear Lever Knob in Black Perforated Leather, Heated Front Seats, Heated Front and Outer Rear Seats, High Multi-Function 3-Spoke Leather Steering Wheel with Grips in Perforated Leather and S Badging with Gear-Shift Paddles, Illuminated Door Sill Trims with S Logo, Inlays - Matt Brushed Aluminium, Keyless Go, LED Interior Light Package, Non-Smoking Package, Pedals and Footrest - Stainless Steel, Split-Folding 2-Seater Rear Seat Bench in 3 Parts - 40-20-40 with Rear Centre Armrest, Tool Kit and Car Jack, Electromechanical Power Steering, Sport Suspension, 6-Airbag System, ABS - Anti-Lock Braking System, Anti-Theft Alarm, ESC - Electronic Stabilisation Control inc ABS - ASR and EDL, Electromechanical Parking Brake, First Aid Kit and Warning Triangle, ISOFIX Child Seat Mounting and Top Tether, Multi Collision Brake Assist, Parking System Plus, Pop-Up Bonnet for Pedestrian Protection, Pre-Sense City, Seat Belt Monitoring, Variable Restraint System</ExtraFeatures>
    <Reg>BK68 EPN</Reg>
    <Video></Video>
    <MetaTag>Audi A5 2.0 TFSI S line S Tronic Euro 6 (s/s) 2dr Petrol Automatic Black</MetaTag>
    <Tax>195</Tax>
    <Insurance>31E</Insurance>
    <Mpg>50.4</Mpg>
    <AT>https://www.autotrader.co.uk/car-details/202602260250073?journey=DEALER_STOCK_LIST_JOURNEY&amp;sort=price-asc&amp;twcs=true&amp;searchId=a52dc470-7aa8-4a85-9606-6db515916294&amp;advertising-location=at_profile_cars&amp;advertising-location=at_cars&amp;page=1&amp;postcode=ts233ta&amp;fromsra=&amp;fromDealerSearchResults=&amp;backLinkQueryParams=advertising-location%3Dat_cars%26advertising-location%3Dat_profile_cars%26onesearchad%3DUsed%26onesearchad%3DNearly%2520New%26onesearchad%3DNew%26postcode%3Dts233ta%26retailerId%3D10041187%26sort%3Dprice-asc%26flrfc%3D1&amp;calc-deposit=1100&amp;calc-term=48&amp;calc-mileage=10000</AT>
    <Description>
      - Stunning Automatic Audi A5 S line finished in sleek black, combining sharp coupe styling with everyday practicality. This 68-plate example offers the perfect balance of performance, comfort and premium build quality.
      - Powered by the responsive 2.0 TFSI petrol engine, it delivers smooth acceleration and confident motorway cruising while remaining economical for its class. The S line specification adds sporty styling and upgraded suspension for a more dynamic drive.
      - 🔥 Key Features:
      - S line exterior styling and badging
      - LED headlights and rear lights
      - 20” S line diamond cut alloy wheels
      - Sport suspension
      - Half leather / Alcantara S line sports seats
      - Multifunction steering wheel
      - Audi MMI infotainment system
      - Heated seats.
      - Bluetooth connectivity
      - Cruise control
      - Dual-zone climate control
      - Front and rear parking sensors
      - The cabin is refined and driver-focused, with high-quality materials throughout and excellent comfort for both driver and passengers. The boot offers generous space, making this car as practical as it is stylish.
      - ✅ 74,000 miles
      - ✅ Mot will be renewed.
      - ✅ Drives superbly
      - This A5 S line is ideal for anyone looking for a premium, sporty coupe with strong road presence and everyday usability.
    </Description>
    <Image>https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/a609239266f547cf8b5aab27a953efee.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/2657e44b5e9742649d415b524be39e46.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/d6a529a08395498281a811e60f1c3f47.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/47a4208eab5d4a55a8fe5a0e9edd1dbc.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/191c66c5c118493f817ca41c0209548d.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/684bc49660a948899643f7409ee0b8ca.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/63f4ecec26b941b49edab3246d96a611.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/19662b0388a8433896aa74338cfd36fa.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/68f08ac78c924a228957008be98e6e0c.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/46b0fb343f184d1eba9fac21abaddc3a.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/b8e9cc015d774f9e8342ff1203cc4236.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/2b6571601c19418ca1bb170a61884d04.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/ae03e88c98484330901c47ab38a42f4c.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/c5232fe43d8342698e1d3b91a113d834.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/3a52896362bf483eb07f5cc5f2ad1a0e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/5f6e91126f9345ceb55c06db47aa355f.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/d1c65b9d70664352af2ae4fd23ea25ad.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/5607127e82884117bf89bf0dce40f2bd.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/a811d29169444ac2b6aa2df1c286f1d5.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/f6efaf97b4064d368c69a08a933055b3.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/137680d096e34c3491cb5a835a0963f7.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/4c047275c852421d841b3a3a9d068f0c.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/4d6a6fcff13948d1ad7d78b698affbe0.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/a5c289e4ce3447e58676c7fee7ef143a.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/2414432073ac41fab8cb217ca49a185c.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/2bba470f511e4e57a4955e82eb6e3243.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/4767b267c43e4178b973240ce2f0b9bd.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/77c7d81aea704b64aca99117e51adadc.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/1357f42988ba490ba8a008f1b920a02e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/33f923c78857448792aad31d9a9d0adc.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/4ed9632ce0594915a8c9dc543530b5df.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/258d14a30bfb4887bb3a92a3c24926eb.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/5de104f3db9b46bfb7221e862598614b.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/07eee892c749412e8a4143affb06e043.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/df830a2dca2944128005617f91692e90.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/20b80c49096f405699d6e8fc2ac02d6a.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/b277fdc68acc42d7b8b41971b9049102.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/3a3cddf5886f46ab926050e2d053cce3.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/a1c2c30d0ced4f0a90435d101342e3cf.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/5546565135294fab8d80bf183989ef6e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/69903798e79d44bba8b5030ea0ffd2d0.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/aadd67e7730f44bcbcc0c75ed4bd2e56.jpg</Image>
  </Car>
  <Car>
    <ID>3</ID>
    <Name>Volkswagen</Name>
    <Model>CC</Model>
    <FullModel>2.0 TDI BlueMotion Tech GT Euro 5 (s/s) 4dr</FullModel>
    <EyeCatcher>CLUTCH KIT✅6M W'NTY✅£35 R’TAX</EyeCatcher>
    <Value>5499</Value>
    <Mileage>90500</Mileage>
    <YearOfManu>2014</YearOfManu>
    <CatStat>HPI Clear</CatStat>
    <FuelType>Diesel</FuelType>
    <Transmission>Manual</Transmission>
    <Colour>Grey</Colour>
    <ExtraFeatures>12V Socket - Centre Console, Bluetooth Telephone Preparation for Hands Free Profile Enabled Telephones, Colour Screen - 5in, DAB+ - Digital Radio Reception, Dash-mounted MP3 Compatible CD Player, MDI - Multi Device Interface, RNS 315 Touch Screen Satellite Navigation and Radio System, SD Card Reader, Speakers x8, Analogue Clock, Cruise Control, Driver Alert System, Flat Tyre Indicator, Multifunction Computer - Colour, Parking Sensors - Front and Rear, Parking Sensors - Rear, Tyre Pressure Indicator, Warning Light for Low Washer Fluid, Warning Lights for Open Boot Lid and Doors, 18in Alloy Wheels - Chicago, 18in Alloy Wheels - Interlagos, Anti-Theft Wheel Bolts, Body Coloured Door Handles, Bumpers - Body Coloured Front and Bumper Strips, Door Mirrors - Body Coloured with Integrated Indicators LED, Door Mirrors - Electrically Adjustable and Heated, Electric Windows - Front and Rear, Grey exterior colour, Heated Windscreen Washer Jets, Radiator Grille - Gloss Black with Chrome Trimmed Surround and Louvres, Spare Wheel - Full Size Alloy, Tinted Glass - Heat Insulating Rear 65 Percent Light Absorbing from B Pillar Backwards, Bi-Xenon Headlights, Daytime Running Lights, Front Fog Lights, Headlight Washer System, Headlights - Automatic Range Adjustment, Headlights - Coming-Leaving Home Function, Headlights - Dusk Sensor - Automatic Driving Lights, High Level 3rd Brake Light, Rear Tail Lights and Rear Number Plate Lights - LED, 2 Zone Electronic Climate Control with Automatic Air Recirculation, Armrest - Front Centre with Storage Compartment, Automatic Dimming Rear View Mirror, Black full leather interior, Carpet Mats - Front and Rear, Cup Holders - Front x2, Cup Holders - Rear x2, Drivers Seat Height Adjustment, Front Seat Back Storage Pockets, Glovebox - Illuminated - Cooled - Lockable, Head Restraints - Front 4-Way Adjustment, Heated Front Seats, Height and Reach Adjustable Steering Column, Interior Lighting - Front and Rear with Interior Delay and Dimming Function, Intermittent Windscreen Wiper Control, Leather Trimmed Three-Spoke Steering Wheel and Gear Knob, Load Lashing Points x2 in Luggage Compartment, Load-Through Provision, Nappa Leather - Black, Press and Drive Key, Rain Sensor, Reading Lights - Front x2, Reading Lights - Rear, Rear Centre Armrest, Seats - Drivers 6-Way Electric Adjustment, Seats - Front Lumbar Support, Seats - Front Sports, Seats - Height Adjustment - Front Passenger, Seats - Split Folding Rear, Stainless Steel Door Sills - Front and Rear, Steering Wheel - Multifunction, Storage Compartment in Roof Console, Storage Compartments in Doors, Storage Tray in Centre Console, Sun Visors - Vanity Mirrors and Illuminated, Three Rear Head Restraints, Trim - Interior - Dark Brushed Aluminium Decorative Inserts in Dashboard-Centre Console and Doors, Two Rear Air Vents, Power Assisted Steering - Speed Sensitive, Suspension - Sports - Lowered by Approx 15mm, ABS - Anti-Lock Braking System, ASR - Anti Slip Regulation, Airbags - Curtain, Airbags - Driver, Airbags - Front Passenger, Airbags - Front Passenger with Deactivation Switch, Airbags - Front Seat Side Impact, Alarm with Interior Protection, BAS - Brake Assist System, Central Locking with Remote Control, Countersteer Support, Differential Lock - Electronic, Door Side Impact Protection, EBD - Electronic Brake Pressure Distribution, ESP - Electronic Stability Programme, Electronic Engine Immobiliser, Electronic Parking Brake with Auto Hold Function, Height-Adjustable Front Three-Point Seat Belts with Tensioners, Hill Hold Assist, ISOFIX Child Seat Preparation - Outer Rear, Seatbelt Reminder, Warning Triangle</ExtraFeatures>
    <Reg>VN64 AOV</Reg>
    <Video></Video>
    <MetaTag>Volkswagen CC 2.0 TDI BlueMotion Tech GT Euro 5 (s/s) 4dr Diesel Manual Grey</MetaTag>
    <Tax>£35</Tax>
    <Insurance>24E</Insurance>
    <Mpg>61.4</Mpg>
    <AT>autotrader.co.uk/car-details/202602210117186?journey=DEALER_STOCK_LIST_JOURNEY&amp;sort=price-asc&amp;twcs=true&amp;searchId=62e0f2d0-358e-41e5-96c5-0bcc97cbfb1e&amp;advertising-location=at_profile_cars&amp;advertising-location=at_cars&amp;page=1&amp;postcode=ts233ta&amp;fromsra&amp;fromDealerSearchResults&amp;backLinkQueryParams=advertising-location%3Dat_cars%26advertising-location%3Dat_profile_cars%26onesearchad%3DUsed%26onesearchad%3DNearly%2520New%26onesearchad%3DNew%26postcode%3Dts233ta%26retailerId%3D10041187%26sort%3Dprice-asc%26flrfc%3D1</AT>
    <Description>
      - Available now is this sleek and well-presented 2014 (64) Volkswagen CC 2.0 TDI BlueMotion Tech GT, a stylish executive coupe-saloon offering strong performance, excellent comfort, and impressive fuel economy.
      - Powered by the refined 2.0 TDI diesel engine, it delivers smooth power, strong torque, and great MPG — perfect for motorway driving, commuting, or anyone wanting executive comfort with sporty styling.
      - ✅ GT Spec • Executive Coupe Styling • Excellent MPG
      - Key Features Include:
      - • GT specification
      - • Leather interior
      - • Heated front seats
      - • Touchscreen infotainment system
      - • Satellite navigation
      - • Bluetooth and media connectivity
      - • Cruise control
      - • Dual-zone climate control
      - • Front and rear parking sensors
      - • Alloy wheels
      - • Multifunction steering wheel
      - • Electric windows and mirrors
      - • ISOFIX
      - • LED daytime running lights
      - Drives beautifully — smooth, refined, and comfortable. No warning lights or mechanical issues.
      - • Recently serviced and inspected
      - • MOT expires 03/11/2026
      - ✅ Drive away today – reserve VN64 AOV with a refundable £100 deposit (TandCs apply).
      - 🚚 Nationwide delivery available at competitive rates.
      - ⸻
      - Why Buy from AW Trade Centre?
      - We provide:
      - • Full mechanical inspection
      - • Free comprehensive warranty
      - • HPI clear vehicles (unless otherwise stated)
      - • Fresh valet inside and out
      - • Friendly, honest, and pressure-free service
      - 📞 Call or message us today to arrange a viewing or reserve this Volkswagen CC 2.0 TDI GT.
    </Description>
    <Image>https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/ed74d847a13c434d8baf7738cd559346.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/8d8b580bde1a42e1bdd4c309171d9144.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/8b56548b62584bd3a1328817fa998182.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/1a880574af1e4ff7857b740c70a6bb58.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/1697ba28d62546d48364ee16b8e6de93.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/332776d7ceb24c608cb2e32e9dad5c77.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/bb0a4d4d4c644b5aa036b71528def0a8.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/f64f5c91d0f54822aeb2bf8d5618ab39.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/8c30db268be3423eb0582800a0f1d868.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/9c7d4c4f3f9a432cbc8f1c305c2fea15.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/3cc9026b37784acb9bea7945ca2ce761.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/381f7aed7b26435bba7d4d43d58f2d7e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/b43723b067d34371af962e70361a3610.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/f67a95f287bf49eb87618ecce0e0a35e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/40a734da235647fc835d3c33ae3fb244.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/bb718284bcdb490880d066ceb8d8da01.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/0d8fca2f48e54005963ab45d4e559638.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/73bd5de0d4a54dc19f043dd3d80a6c8b.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/3b6d04dd380b4cb680dbabedb0a3478c.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/ed432e9b63e44b6683db18929a12380b.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/1e5185fd65874a8583a82edaff11d13b.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/de2048d167fe46a9ad81ccea5d2b9896.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/bb7af76d1bff4b3ebab26cdea26a754a.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/555a2c623f8148c6a8eb1041b2397234.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/ef76bb1937fd4f2688c82ec9d42f6a67.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/9f93fb8b080b43289624b6cb6fb313ae.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/124f39512e8545b3ae6afde1301329a1.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/39e20e4e25084a11b9946aa2fa9d8fff.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/1507f6d9ac204d5c93c9b73af03ecb76.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/d0a590d0b442418f8cf70785dff5f15c.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/23ca7080bf6f4dd2b5743d956f7ad1db.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/9254e49a1e884737b83083e4d70a8030.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/312c2ea1f2544f1881d9ef468d1e1a32.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/ce5dd2784df646648354302b7b58dcf3.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/dd10192b54294af7bbc05d35ab81db80.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/75b0679c56be492187f0b397f1c2193a.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/8aee488fbfed4ca4a7eb8d1fefc32dae.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/a22becacbeae4841947b077d3e04cd9c.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/288e948f767a49d99653b198e1d81551.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/ba271b777b50494dbc64a3e9688f1133.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/7093cc354c324bdd91b8aa81b078520b.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/0882215eff054e7788e19f09e71a74ec.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/7fd4f4db94a14f118d97764b69a586d2.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/fbe04a77843d4d02b8328ea1f8fbe134.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/7cbbf1f2698a4e07ba7131afaa585e3d.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/72a6c38f43e34b699a7c78d5020cb3f0.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/c41ff0b2dfd9417b96ac140e2805fa96.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/ee56d9e5b4ed4ac78735574f110d9148.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/fb5f019080ca4d87a918e4b07c4ad5ac.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/21924a44dcc1462e94783a81968d097a.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/8fc3a859f17b432b97e6da71b1f776a4.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/f809876315334781b21fa9ce8619f8bd.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/951bd16b617c48f1bac13cb00d32864d.jpg</Image>
  </Car>
  <Car>
    <ID>4</ID>
    <Name>Nissan</Name>
    <Model>X-Trail</Model>
    <FullModel>1.6 dCi n-tec Euro 5 (s/s) 5dr</FullModel>
    <EyeCatcher>SUNROOF✅360 CAMERA✅7 SEATER✅</EyeCatcher>
    <Value>4599</Value>
    <Mileage>120500</Mileage>
    <YearOfManu>2015</YearOfManu>
    <CatStat>Clear</CatStat>
    <FuelType>Diesel</FuelType>
    <Transmission>Manual</Transmission>
    <Colour>Grey</Colour>
    <ExtraFeatures></ExtraFeatures>
    <Reg>NX15HNH</Reg>
    <Video></Video>
    <MetaTag></MetaTag>
    <Tax>165</Tax>
    <Insurance>17E</Insurance>
    <Mpg>57.6</Mpg>
    <AT>https://www.autotrader.co.uk/car-details/202601279453429?journey=DEALER_STOCK_LIST_JOURNEY&amp;sort=price-asc&amp;twcs=true&amp;searchId=60c810d7-39ea-4c6e-a86d-1c86287ba195&amp;advertising-location=at_profile_cars&amp;advertising-location=at_cars&amp;page=1&amp;postcode=ts233ta&amp;fromsra=&amp;fromDealerSearchResults=&amp;backLinkQueryParams=advertising-location%3Dat_cars%26advertising-location%3Dat_profile_cars%26onesearchad%3DUsed%26onesearchad%3DNearly%2520New%26onesearchad%3DNew%26postcode%3Dts233ta%26retailerId%3D10041187%26sort%3Dprice-asc%26flrfc%3D1&amp;calc-deposit=500&amp;calc-term=48&amp;calc-mileage=10000&amp;calc-selected-product=HP</AT>
    <Description>
      - Available now is this spacious and well-equipped 2015 Nissan X-Trail 1.6 dCi n-tec (7 Seater), a practical and comfortable SUV offering excellent fuel economy, modern technology, and superb everyday usability for families.
      - Powered by the efficient 1.6 dCi diesel engine, it delivers strong MPG and smooth motorway cruising, making it ideal for family use, long-distance driving, or anyone needing extra space.
      - ✅ 7 Seats • n-tec Spec • Excellent MPG • Spacious SUV
      - Key Features Include:
      - • 7-seat configuration
      - • Touchscreen infotainment system
      - • Satellite navigation
      - • 360° Around View Monitor (reverse camera)
      - • Front and rear parking sensors
      - • Bluetooth and media connectivity
      - • Dual-zone climate control
      - • Cruise control with speed limiter
      - • Panoramic glass roof (if fitted)
      - • Alloy wheels
      - • Multifunction steering wheel
      - • Electric windows and mirrors
      - • ISOFIX
      - • Daytime running lights
      - Drives superb — smooth, comfortable, and economical. No warning lights or mechanical issues.
      - • Recently serviced and inspected
      - • MOT expires 25/01/2027
      - ✅ Drive away today – reserve NX15 HNH with a refundable £100 deposit (TandCs apply).
      - 🚚 Nationwide delivery available at competitive rates.
      - ⸻
      - Why Buy from AW Trade Centre?
      - We provide:
      - • Full mechanical inspection
      - • Free comprehensive warranty
      - • HPI clear vehicles (unless otherwise stated)
      - • Fresh valet inside and out
      - • Friendly, honest, and pressure-free service
      - 📞 Call or message us today to arrange a viewing or reserve this Nissan X-Trail 1.6 dCi n-tec 7 Seater.
    </Description>
    <Image>https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w800/af7abadb9c8e4b66bb4a7f700a138b1f.jpg,
https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w600/57fe9acfccef439b8957fa15987b501c.jpg,
https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w600/4e889c870fda4762b8e72f3319bbfbb3.jpg,
https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w600/97ffad8993244fd4b603d308087246a2.jpg,
https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w600/f8427188b8f64d4ab920b827f35225c9.jpg,
https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w600/30234a47864a4a7b8f80ef4d3bb2e115.jpg,
https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w600/9e9d68a1cd31489bad62dac5d65761ad.jpg</Image>
  </Car>
  <Car>
    <ID>5</ID>
    <Name>Toyota</Name>
    <Model>AYGO</Model>
    <FullModel>1.0 VVT-i + Euro 4 3dr</FullModel>
    <EyeCatcher>DELIVERY✅£20 R’TAX</EyeCatcher>
    <Value>1399</Value>
    <Mileage>75000</Mileage>
    <YearOfManu>2007</YearOfManu>
    <CatStat>Clear</CatStat>
    <FuelType>Petrol</FuelType>
    <Transmission>Manual</Transmission>
    <Colour>Silver</Colour>
    <ExtraFeatures></ExtraFeatures>
    <Reg>SH57PNX</Reg>
    <Video></Video>
    <MetaTag></MetaTag>
    <Tax>20</Tax>
    <Insurance>02E</Insurance>
    <Mpg>62.8</Mpg>
    <AT>https://www.autotrader.co.uk/car-details/202601299525378?journey=DEALER_STOCK_LIST_JOURNEY&amp;sort=price-asc&amp;twcs=true&amp;searchId=371eee0c-3d74-4249-a846-662400bce2b2&amp;advertising-location=at_profile_cars&amp;advertising-location=at_cars&amp;page=1&amp;postcode=ts233ta&amp;fromsra=&amp;fromDealerSearchResults=&amp;backLinkQueryParams=advertising-location%3Dat_cars%26advertising-location%3Dat_profile_cars%26onesearchad%3DUsed%26onesearchad%3DNearly%2520New%26onesearchad%3DNew%26postcode%3Dts233ta%26retailerId%3D10041187%26sort%3Dprice-asc%26flrfc%3D1&amp;calc-deposit=200&amp;calc-term=48&amp;calc-mileage=10000</AT>
    <Description>
      - Available now is this ultra-economical and reliable 2007 (57) Toyota AYGO 1.0 VVT-i +, a perfect city car known for its very low running costs, cheap insurance, and excellent reliability.
      - Powered by the efficient 1.0 VVT-i petrol engine, it’s easy to drive, extremely economical, and ideal for new drivers, city driving, or anyone looking for a cheap-to-run daily car.
      - ✅ £20 yearly road tax • Low insurance • Excellent MPG
      - Key Features Include:
      - • + specification
      - • Air conditioning
      - • Electric windows
      - • Remote central locking
      - • Radio / CD player
      - • Split folding rear seats
      - • ISOFIX
      - • Power steering
      - Drives great — smooth, light, and very economical.
      - • Recently serviced and inspected
      - • MOT expires 5/10/2026
      - ✅ Drive away today – reserve SH57 PNX with a refundable £100 deposit (TandCs apply).
      - 🚚 Nationwide delivery available at competitive rates.
      - ⸻
      - Why Buy from AW Trade Centre?
      - We provide:
      - • Full mechanical inspection
      - • HPI clear vehicles (unless otherwise stated)
      - • Fresh valet inside and out
      - • Friendly, honest, and pressure-free service
      - 📞 Call or message us today to arrange a viewing or reserve this Toyota AYGO 1.0 VVT-i +.
    </Description>
    <Image>https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w800/34fedc19ac2b4917bfaed842c15bb70f.jpg,
https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w600/90228c2335624ef488bfe022d41ff8be.jpg,
https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w600/0491cb8fe42a4268af6b9b6fe03a0d69.jpg,
https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w600/4897c09aa45c45669ea1d3550e7ceb77.jpg,
https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w600/205f86c3c6924bc0bb2c8e1345b3b3ad.jpg,
https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w600/d19511dc71e640b4bb0d8dc7d5b9bbca.jpg,
https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w600/6c638d1226774e06b6fffca7c2b43b8a.jpg</Image>
  </Car>
  <Car>
    <ID>6</ID>
    <Name>Ford</Name>
    <Model>Fiesta</Model>
    <FullModel>1.4 Titanium 5dr</FullModel>
    <EyeCatcher>FULL MOT✅6M WARRANTY✅DELIVERY✅</EyeCatcher>
    <Value>2499</Value>
    <Mileage>99900</Mileage>
    <YearOfManu>2011</YearOfManu>
    <CatStat>Clear</CatStat>
    <FuelType>Petrol</FuelType>
    <Transmission>Manual</Transmission>
    <Colour>Blue</Colour>
    <ExtraFeatures></ExtraFeatures>
    <Reg>PO11TNZ</Reg>
    <Video></Video>
    <MetaTag></MetaTag>
    <Tax>195</Tax>
    <Insurance>09E</Insurance>
    <Mpg>49.6</Mpg>
    <AT>https://www.autotrader.co.uk/car-details/202601299524949?journey=DEALER_STOCK_LIST_JOURNEY&amp;sort=price-asc&amp;twcs=true&amp;searchId=250c952e-c652-467d-8a2a-616363e1e88d&amp;advertising-location=at_profile_cars&amp;advertising-location=at_cars&amp;page=1&amp;postcode=ts233ta&amp;fromsra=&amp;fromDealerSearchResults=&amp;backLinkQueryParams=advertising-location%3Dat_cars%26advertising-location%3Dat_profile_cars%26onesearchad%3DUsed%26onesearchad%3DNearly%2520New%26onesearchad%3DNew%26postcode%3Dts233ta%26retailerId%3D10041187%26sort%3Dprice-asc%26flrfc%3D1&amp;calc-deposit=250&amp;calc-term=48&amp;calc-mileage=10000</AT>
    <Description>
      - Available now is this smart and economical 2011 (61) Ford Fiesta 1.4 Titanium (5-Door), a reliable and practical hatchback offering low running costs, great driving comfort, and excellent everyday usability.
      - Powered by the proven 1.4 petrol engine, it’s smooth, easy to drive, and cheap to insure — making it ideal for new drivers, commuting, or a dependable family runaround.
      - ✅ Low insurance • Great MPG • Practical 5-door
      - Key Features Include:
      - • Rear parking sensors
      - • Power folding door mirrors
      - • Titanium specification
      - • Alloy wheels
      - • Air conditioning
      - • Bluetooth and media connectivity (if fitted)
      - • Heated front windscreen
      - • Multifunction steering wheel
      - • Electric windows and mirrors
      - • Remote central locking
      - • ISOFIX
      - • Daytime running lights
      - Drives great — smooth, comfortable, and economical. No warning lights or mechanical issues.
      - • Recently serviced and inspected
      - • MOT to be renewed at point of sale
      - ✅ Drive away today – reserve PO11 TNZ with a refundable £100 deposit (TandCs apply).
      - 🚚 Nationwide delivery available at competitive rates.
      - ⸻
      - Why Buy from AW Trade Centre?
      - We provide:
      - • Full mechanical inspection
      - • Free comprehensive warranty
      - • HPI clear vehicles (unless otherwise stated)
      - • Fresh valet inside and out
      - • Friendly, honest, and pressure-free service
      - 📞 Call or message us today to arrange a viewing or reserve this Ford Fiesta 1.4 Titanium 5-Door.
    </Description>
    <Image>https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w800/13a444da494c45a5bbc2f78aae41b982.jpg,
https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w600/088182def48548b79580a5a39edc8453.jpg,
https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w600/da1a037dda564e80810c697d124a15a7.jpg,
https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w600/edb959cbe6fe400ab396c6978a4eda9a.jpg,
https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w600/1ca4041497dc4235984743d691069f9e.jpg,
https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w600/2c3995e834f545e1b7b9a4537ee20882.jpg,
https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w600/71dc21ca09dc403397a7dcecb6bbc349.jpg</Image>
  </Car>
  <Car>
    <ID>7</ID>
    <Name>Mercedes-Benz</Name>
    <Model>C Class</Model>
    <FullModel>2.1 C250 CDI BlueEfficiency Sport G-Tronic+ Euro 5 (s/s) 4dr</FullModel>
    <EyeCatcher>GBOX SERVICE✅ALLOY REFUR✅2KEYS</EyeCatcher>
    <Value>5099</Value>
    <Mileage>109600</Mileage>
    <YearOfManu>2012</YearOfManu>
    <CatStat>Clear</CatStat>
    <FuelType>Diesel</FuelType>
    <Transmission>Automatic</Transmission>
    <Colour>White</Colour>
    <ExtraFeatures></ExtraFeatures>
    <Reg>WG12AAE</Reg>
    <Video>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SknJy1vhakg</Video>
    <MetaTag></MetaTag>
    <Tax>195</Tax>
    <Insurance>38E</Insurance>
    <Mpg>58.9</Mpg>
    <AT>https://www.autotrader.co.uk/car-details/202511238086093?journey=DEALER_STOCK_LIST_JOURNEY&amp;sort=price-asc&amp;twcs=true&amp;searchId=5d20da6f-c344-41f8-aa23-096f7ad1c0c7&amp;advertising-location=at_profile_cars&amp;advertising-location=at_cars&amp;page=1&amp;postcode=TS55EX&amp;fromsra&amp;fromDealerSearchResults&amp;backLinkQueryParams=advertising-location%3Dat_cars%26advertising-location%3Dat_profile_cars%26onesearchad%3DUsed%26onesearchad%3DNearly%2520New%26onesearchad%3DNew%26postcode%3DTS55EX%26retailerId%3D10041187%26sort%3Dprice-asc%26flrfc%3D1</AT>
    <Description>
      
    </Description>
    <Image>https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w800/7421836db9bf483994e5033928d0282e.jpg,
https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w600/7fa60ae8d2204ed5a06c551beb6f9c57.jpg,
https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w600/7238708bd8d7410d83e37382921ffc45.jpg,
https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w600/96b3e603733249c9880f0a6811c319fe.jpg,
https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w600/0042d834fb5147e4a609d5a7a3a49f3b.jpg,
https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w600/08f02e79addf4270862a3cc5aa0c7698.jpg,
https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w600/ba5fe941ef824122be6f772325f724aa.jpg</Image>
  </Car>
  <Car>
    <ID>8</ID>
    <Name>SEAT</Name>
    <Model>Leon</Model>
    <FullModel>1.4 TSI ACT FR Euro 6 (s/s) 5dr</FullModel>
    <EyeCatcher>T-BELT ✅FRESH SERVICE✅WARRANTY</EyeCatcher>
    <Value>4850</Value>
    <Mileage>124600</Mileage>
    <YearOfManu>2014</YearOfManu>
    <CatStat>HPI Clear</CatStat>
    <FuelType>Petrol</FuelType>
    <Transmission>Manual</Transmission>
    <Colour>Black</Colour>
    <ExtraFeatures>12V Power Supply in Centre Console - Front, 3.5in Monochrome Drivers Display, AUX-In Port, Bluetooth Audio Streaming, Easy Connect System, FM-AM Radio, Integrated Bluetooth Handsfree System, MP3 Compatible CD Player, Navigation System, Speakers x8, Touch Screen - Colour 5in, USB Port, Cruise Control, Exterior Temperature Indicator, Front Parking Sensors, Gearshift Indicator, Parking Sensors - Front and Rear with Optical Parking System, Rear Parking Sensors, SEAT Drive Profile - Sport-Comfort-Eco-Individual, Trip Computer, Tyre Pressure Monitoring System, Voice Control - In Car Entertaintment, 17in Alloy Wheels - Dynamic, Black exterior colour, Body-Coloured Door Handles, Bumpers - Exclusive FR Front and Rear, Dark Tinted Rear Windows, Door Mirrors - Electrically Folding with Reverse Activated Kerb-View Function, Door Mirrors - with Integrated LED Indicators, Electric Windows - Front and Rear with One-Touch and Anti-Squeeze, Emergency Tyre Repair Kit, Exhaust Pipe - Twin, Gloss Black Pillars, Locking Wheel Bolts, Passenger Door Mirror with Kerb Function when Reversing, Radiator Grille - Chrome Centre Surround, SEAT Logo Tailgate Release, Space Saving Spare Wheel - 16in, Space Saving Spare Wheel - 18in, Daytime Running Lights - Halogen, Front Fog Lights with Cornering Function, Headlights - Electric Range Adjustment, Headlights - Twin Halogen, LED Taillights, Lights Left On Warning Buzzer, Active Front Head Restraints, Ambient Spot Lighting and Footwell Illumination, Armrest - Front with Storage Compartment, Chrome Interior Decorative Mouldings, Cupholders - Front x2, Door Sill Trim - Aluminium, Dual Zone Climate Control, Dust and Pollen Filter, Head Restraints - Height Adjustable Front, Head Restraints - Height Adjustable Rear x3, Height Adjustable Passenger Seat, Height and Reach Adjustable Steering Wheel, Height-Adjustable Drivers Seat, Illuminated Boot, Illuminated Glovebox, Inserts - Dash - Chrome Detailing, Instrument Lighting with Brightness Control, Leather Gear Knob, Leather Handbrake, Leatherette Bolsters, Luggage Compartment - Rings, Reading Light - Front and Rear, Remote Key - Folding x2 with Remote Window Functionality, Seats - Front Lumbar Adjustment, Seats - Pockets on Front Backrest, Seats - Split Folding Rear, Seats - Sports, Steering Wheel - Flat-Bottomed Perforated Leather with Red Stitching and FR Logo, Steering Wheel Mounted Audio and Phone Controls, Sunvisors with Illuminated Vanity Mirrors, Sunvisors with Vanity Mirrors, Electro-Mechanical Power Steering - Speed-Sensitive, Electronic Differential Lock System - XDS, Sports Suspension, Airbags - Curtain, Airbags - Driver, Airbags - Front Passenger, Alarm - Perimeter Tow Away Protection, Anti-Lock Braking System - ABS, Automatic Post-Collision Braking System, Child Locks on Rear Doors, Deadlocks, Drivers Knee Airbag, EBA - Electronic Brake Assist, Electronic Stability Control - ESC, Front Passenger Airbag De-Activation, Front Side Airbags, Hill Hold Control, ISOFIX Points with Top Tether on Rear Seats, Rear Wiper, Remote Central Locking, Seatbelt Reminder - Front, TCS - Traction Control System</ExtraFeatures>
    <Reg>BX64 YBV</Reg>
    <Video></Video>
    <MetaTag>SEAT Leon 1.4 TSI ACT FR Euro 6 (s/s) 5dr Petrol Manual Black</MetaTag>
    <Tax>£20</Tax>
    <Insurance>20E</Insurance>
    <Mpg>53.3</Mpg>
    <AT>https://www.autotrader.co.uk/car-details/202602049681863?journey=DEALER_STOCK_LIST_JOURNEY&amp;sort=price-asc&amp;twcs=true&amp;searchId=ac425780-849d-417e-8f8c-c189634cb5c8&amp;advertising-location=at_profile_cars&amp;advertising-location=at_cars&amp;page=1&amp;postcode=ts233ta&amp;fromsra=&amp;fromDealerSearchResults=&amp;backLinkQueryParams=advertising-location%3Dat_cars%26advertising-location%3Dat_profile_cars%26onesearchad%3DUsed%26onesearchad%3DNearly%2520New%26onesearchad%3DNew%26postcode%3Dts233ta%26retailerId%3D10041187%26sort%3Dprice-asc%26flrfc%3D1&amp;calc-deposit=485&amp;calc-term=48&amp;calc-mileage=10000</AT>
    <Description>
      - Available now is this sporty and well-presented 2014 (64) SEAT Leon 1.4 TSI ACT FR, a stylish hatchback offering strong performance, excellent fuel economy, and sharp FR styling.
      - Powered by the efficient 1.4 TSI ACT petrol engine, it delivers lively performance while maintaining great MPG thanks to Active Cylinder Technology (ACT), making it both fun to drive and economical.
      - ✅ FR Sport Styling • ACT Technology • ULEZ Compliant
      - Key Features Include:
      - • FR sports styling package
      - • 1.4 TSI ACT engine
      - • Sports seats
      - • Touchscreen infotainment system
      - • Bluetooth and media connectivity
      - • Cruise control
      - • Dual-zone climate control
      - • Multifunction steering wheel
      - • Alloy wheels
      - • Electric windows and mirrors
      - • ISOFIX
      - • LED daytime running lights
      - Drives superb — smooth, responsive, and great fun to drive. No warning lights or mechanical issues.
      - • Recently serviced and inspected
      - • MOT expires 7/11/2026
      - ✅ Drive away today – reserve PX64 YBV with a refundable £100 deposit (TandCs apply).
      - 🚚 Nationwide delivery available at competitive rates.
      - ⸻
      - Why Buy from AW Trade Centre?
      - We provide:
      - • Full mechanical inspection
      - • Free comprehensive warranty
      - • HPI clear vehicles (unless otherwise stated)
      - • Fresh valet inside and out
      - • Friendly, honest, and pressure-free service
      - 📞 Call or message us today to arrange a viewing or reserve this SEAT Leon 1.4 TSI ACT FR.
    </Description>
    <Image>https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/95f8a05bb9dc4feea761206a9455ed9e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/5580bf66d1a94f0889f69b4a3c9dc5b4.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/fba184cbec62454f9acf5cb210a920f5.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/86c7016348ae41f38e791ce5e81ce31e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/24525dd0dea248fd9ee230f5acfc8228.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/d606b781d95148f88bec116d5b9c53dc.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/9e2fb318fa934d2391e81ffbaf073559.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/29f53d42319f47d4b66dc3e10dc4de37.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/bfe839f3818c442692de57cb4bef9618.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/16f5d2a123f244279ceb35030b46af8c.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/08aa70a0418e4eae8e2a195e75f08762.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/d8301497796f436eb4610b9749ed5854.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/abd3f545923b4336907ec699bf418604.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/905f16cae27b4f2aae346117046b3f30.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/828425742e7141b2a5bc1962dd629f27.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/68a7c09580d54e129f45a14e4bd64aee.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/fcdac78ebc1d4e36bf850348eab64228.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/48dd5858f9a040fa86f4f8453854b9ab.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/3f53dff3a608425eada7ddaaed17050e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/dc3855c810244463933146a2ae694149.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/8f2c390662ae454eae233ce18af924fe.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/cfe593c275a749f1be33130c5c3e19a7.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/9c8d45a0d99f4589b20d86f76742dde7.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/d349bb1015f3429a98bb7d5ee2933cb1.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/0847473281a0443f979ee199bbd3e983.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/90bd16364baf44cfabd2cb650a652465.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/52b5de3c54f14491aaf62242406390d1.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/df4b53945c9e4656a5b7e82a0965eb7b.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/67bf12ad2e2442b080d577c51e243116.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/f04e01918b094249a57e4326ecd1cdca.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/6c0d13c101da4b6fa7b3b4074f43af5e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/5afc2367af4d45bb9b16c4173933db33.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/21690669b84e4d2ea1e9571a696ecf3a.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/3a8881a1d6474ff185bb12843ffaf149.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/e63d74321d694978937c4bcb35a25289.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/e7c387bd1d524532a06e189e90ebe60d.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/559cb9f1e6124531bd6c36a8904a37d0.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/91b006bda0d64a189adfdf6d213a78e8.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/d112d50edfa349c9b77bb078c5edc1e6.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/ec1ae64b482141d98465c857bfc98df9.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/8a5e0534acf4491fbb5aa55615345104.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/6fd4411ca5f540b3a419506a366e25ac.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/c4a45587a004414386678697ea2ca540.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/12dd008d325c462cb6c566fa1e1b0072.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/0808f58a54254eb7add2257f17800d52.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/15bd0e15411c49f493e18ae5e227175d.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/2fce46be0b2445a99f91eaabbd7da096.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/2d6000d1bc0f48ee9e52c62fd8eeff2a.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/bd6351f82cce43ceb2b8c859ec970d20.jpg</Image>
  </Car>
  <Car>
    <ID>9</ID>
    <Name>Audi</Name>
    <Model>Q7</Model>
    <FullModel>3.0 TDI V6 S line Tiptronic quattro Euro 5 (s/s) 5dr</FullModel>
    <EyeCatcher>✅READ DESC✅</EyeCatcher>
    <Value>5500</Value>
    <Mileage>123900</Mileage>
    <YearOfManu>2011</YearOfManu>
    <CatStat>HPI Clear</CatStat>
    <FuelType>Diesel</FuelType>
    <Transmission>Automatic</Transmission>
    <Colour>Black</Colour>
    <ExtraFeatures>12V Power Socket, 12V Power Socket - Luggage Compartment, BOSE Surround Sound System, CD/Radio, MMI Radio Plus with DSP Sound System, Mobile Telephone Preparation - Bluetooth Interface, Acoustic Parking System - Rear, Audi Parking System Plus, Cruise Control, Drivers Information System - DIS, 20in Alloy Wheels - 5-Spoke Design, Black Roof Rails, Black exterior colour, Door Mirrors - Heated-Electrically Adjustable-Folding, Door Mirrors - Heated-Electrically Adjustable-Folding-Auto-Dimming, Electric Windows - Front and Rear, Panoramic Glass Sunroof, Panoramic Sunroof - Dark Tinted, Privacy Glass, Front Fog Lights, Headlights - Automatic Adjustment, Headlights - Bi-Xenon Plus, Headlights Washers, Auto-Dimming Rear-View Mirror, Automatic Wipers with Rain Sensor, Black full leather interior, Cloth Headlining in Black, Comfort Front Centre Armrest, Cup Holders - Centre Console, Dual-Zone Electronic Climate Control, Electrically Adjustable 4-Way Lumbar Support, Heated Front Seats, Inlays - Matt Brushed Aluminium, Lighting Package, Seats - Front Electric Adjustment, Steering Wheel - 3-Spoke Leather-Multi-Function-Shift Paddles, Steering Wheel - Multi-function, Adaptive Air Suspension, Power Steering - Servotronic Speed-Dependent, ABS - Anti-Lock Braking System, Airbags - Driver, Airbags - Front Passenger, Airbags - Front Side System, Airbags - Sideguard Curtain, Alarm - Thatcham Category 1, EBD - Electronic Brakeforce Distribution, ESP - Electronic Stability Programme, ISOFIX - front passenger second and third row seats with passenger airbag deactivation switch, Remote Central Locking</ExtraFeatures>
    <Reg>LM61 ERX</Reg>
    <Video></Video>
    <MetaTag>Audi Q7 3.0 TDI V6 S line Tiptronic quattro Euro 5 (s/s) 5dr Diesel Automatic Black</MetaTag>
    <Tax>£395</Tax>
    <Insurance>41E</Insurance>
    <Mpg>38.2</Mpg>
    <AT>https://www.autotrader.co.uk/car-details/202601289486380?journey=DEALER_STOCK_LIST_JOURNEY&amp;sort=price-asc&amp;twcs=true&amp;searchId=58cec8de-a3ff-4ced-b165-f0da32c82762&amp;advertising-location=at_profile_cars&amp;advertising-location=at_cars&amp;page=1&amp;postcode=ts233ta&amp;fromsra=&amp;fromDealerSearchResults=&amp;backLinkQueryParams=advertising-location%3Dat_cars%26advertising-location%3Dat_profile_cars%26onesearchad%3DUsed%26onesearchad%3DNearly%2520New%26onesearchad%3DNew%26postcode%3Dts233ta%26retailerId%3D10041187%26sort%3Dprice-asc%26flrfc%3D1&amp;calc-deposit=550&amp;calc-term=48&amp;calc-mileage=10000</AT>
    <Description>
      - ✅✅SPARES OR REPAIRS DUE TO AGE AND MILEAGE✅✅
      - ✅✅£1800 BELOW RETAIL VALUATION✅✅
      - Available now is this powerful and luxurious 2011 (61) Audi Q7 3.0 TDI V6 S line Tiptronic quattro, a full-size premium SUV offering exceptional comfort, strong performance, and outstanding all-weather capability.
      - Powered by the 3.0 V6 TDI diesel engine paired with the smooth Tiptronic automatic gearbox and Audi’s legendary quattro four-wheel drive, it delivers effortless acceleration, confident handling, and impressive towing capability.
      - ✅ V6 Power • S line Spec • quattro 4WD • Luxury SUV
      - Key Features Include:
      - • 6-stage heated seats
      - • Electric seats with memory function
      - • Reverse camera
      - • BOSE surround sound system
      - • Satellite navigation system
      - • S line exterior and interior styling
      - • Tiptronic automatic transmission
      - • quattro four-wheel drive
      - • Full leather S line sports seats
      - • Dual-zone climate control
      - • Cruise control
      - • Front and rear parking sensors
      - • Xenon headlights with LED daytime running lights
      - • Power folding door mirrors
      - • Multifunction steering wheel
      - • Alloy wheels
      - • Electric windows and mirrors
      - • ISOFIX
      - Drives superb — smooth, powerful, and extremely comfortable. No warning lights or mechanical issues.
      - • Recently serviced and inspected
      - • MOT expires July 2026
      - ✅ Drive away today – reserve LM61 ERX with a refundable £100 deposit (TandCs apply).
      - 🚚 Nationwide delivery available at competitive rates.
      - ⸻
      - 📞 Call or message us today to arrange a viewing or reserve this Audi Q7 3.0 TDI S line quattro Auto.
    </Description>
    <Image>https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/1f2595dcaf4c44769111448abc9266c2.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/640b54d2e7774b05a2242e0c736c7c0e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/48bd1b8075754f4c91b7634c923e0a7e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/c221d0b39f674d67a9541dce6665d061.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/539a8b5e98284ae8997c6397fa57e9ae.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/8b63869bd9664083916a2db5fdd2755b.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/f5673bbdb3a14809bf2712af9754f685.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/b5ded8f9d21a487c814e74c047ddcea1.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/99fc81b09e74487d84fde0a5068e0728.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/302f93bcf8894351a3bf8974ff5a87a7.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/09aa72719b4448abb46eca06ca3ed3ae.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/6ceeb40a8a6447ef8b80135b069e3b9b.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/25856186006c41aaac9daa1bd085cf01.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/e4ece768e8794ec4b21537a37e3d19af.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/352cd0c62e4d42e0a83529788c185316.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/065d323585f84788971c8e476e84bef3.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/0ff3535ea547487eb6b8e9ed49861153.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/ce9fe493538744039f28508230aac1bf.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/3f137da6e3dc4ef6bca98efc9d566694.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/cd7932d2451c4d1cad86b7cbc8c36f4e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/23f98eca05ee40c986888d49a1f90d90.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/663fa1cddb384afda1060bd4c98ce480.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/0510539d17234e57a0eea8acb0213f5b.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/cb12777fe8f64a6dbddad896dd9af683.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/8d809ed844d248c4907071107514f6ce.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/6855b7e6ce2442b88a9818e9535a34b6.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/3e740fb926674d908a5cdecd5b288b80.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/60aef4ee95154d7a923e4fff9048c02e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/eb95fac5aa1d4b708060061918686aef.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/4e2cb51a1a1d4049b513ae21d2c08291.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/9301e4b2ae9d4bc192e8c23a59ab378f.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/96d5e5f4b8424d92bd68437f206d9468.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/3ed7c89d24744bf19d802a5442cc7b5e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/38244f54429348deadc0112c2e625e52.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/9bf702d2ae3c49f184b9ef341a88e443.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/8d01862b4e5049a495e4913d3c3b94fc.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/415f74b213714d54b0a60f2aa799c337.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/31ceeec362c446d6a908b786be72fc4d.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/3139cbe8ce204aa0ae703346bc6876b4.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/1a2c94d4dc4c4f049aceefa7ea1ec131.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/1ff40ed1cf394d83a937cdcf899a5294.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/3da24e0ccf184e6897e7df966025eb7e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/780c5443bc8b4018a758f0b169fd7ea9.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/545d5d225d4c4b7ca40e86601052815e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/ad36d8ccd5244a52a5b43f8922c5b2f5.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/fa552e8b92bd4ab89181ea16187cab7c.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/92302793c7764ab0bcafa8ed45c61b4f.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/2e6116e77afd4b46a5dee5b91cf41984.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/80419152f47d446498749e1cd5b31a95.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/446158e50a8f402bae9f182c0dbf1325.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/55176c7d97534d64bfefc3e4368d5ac8.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/3abb3afdbf6f404fae31b188c980c874.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/5b4c397ac3084cc4a20a7d1f3a8d020e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/3206ba78f75941b5a9ba696b6f60d3f0.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/8c83417c482740989024b69d77e2b219.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/3f63cdb9f3884f7f8dcaf377647a7ad3.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/a79d734e795d4e17a6234b221482e4f2.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/2ea26d64e0754c189515041ec04abb38.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/073c4ad9800b40aa844a706ad31d8b08.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/cdc07f7224984423bb2952d94cf27e57.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/c78f40d9a1f24c58a2a8ea0da8a9446c.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/60e0817b980f44af88ac16a34dfe2012.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/23e72a7b00a845868b4475b72f906425.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/2b9f09d1d3204b67a88b0b9e515d6f29.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/8953975a2d784f95b727add2c6745988.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/9b6bda7f8b6340a88561c851ae1a37ba.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/e7177f0749224df8910c72836b1d2d06.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/63cc4345b41140db92fe22e057369d12.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/3561735f383a4c3d9422cfd860c2ffdd.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/1a3fd2faa5e746da9b4cd01f42b8c6b7.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/49eabae3f8c34cfca048e252f3c13946.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/2a471c77e0614a33a75ba11d0bbe2235.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/687cc71e4cc04799b2c200d921c88b50.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/61a155df57ee4f5a81b25a85e5f12af1.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/b3fffab5b98f4d66965340e2b8c7b110.jpg</Image>
  </Car>
  <Car>
    <ID>100</ID>
    <Name>Vauxhall</Name>
    <Model>Corsa</Model>
    <FullModel>1.0i Turbo ecoFLEX Limited Edition Euro 6 (s/s) 3dr</FullModel>
    <EyeCatcher>S’ HISTORY✅WARRANTY</EyeCatcher>
    <Value>4499</Value>
    <Mileage>65200</Mileage>
    <YearOfManu>2016</YearOfManu>
    <CatStat>Clear</CatStat>
    <FuelType>Petrol</FuelType>
    <Transmission>Manual</Transmission>
    <Colour>Black</Colour>
    <ExtraFeatures></ExtraFeatures>
    <Reg>SO65TVU</Reg>
    <Video></Video>
    <MetaTag></MetaTag>
    <Tax>35</Tax>
    <Insurance>13E</Insurance>
    <Mpg>57.6</Mpg>
    <AT>https://www.autotrader.co.uk/car-details/202511107793490?journey=DEALER_STOCK_LIST_JOURNEY&amp;sort=price-asc&amp;twcs=true&amp;searchId=7bfa941a-78ef-4b72-ba19-4704ad91297f&amp;advertising-location=at_profile_cars&amp;advertising-location=at_cars&amp;page=1&amp;postcode=ts233ta&amp;fromsra&amp;fromDealerSearchResults&amp;backLinkQueryParams=advertising-location%3Dat_cars%26advertising-location%3Dat_profile_cars%26onesearchad%3DUsed%26onesearchad%3DNearly%2520New%26onesearchad%3DNew%26postcode%3Dts233ta%26retailerId%3D10041187%26sort%3Dprice-asc%26flrfc%3D1</AT>
    <Description>
      - Description✅✅VEHICLE IS UNDERGOING PREPARATION✅✅
      - Available now is this sporty and stylish 2016 (65) Vauxhall Corsa 1.0i Turbo ecoFLEX Limited Edition, finished in excellent condition inside and out. Powered by the smooth and efficient 1.0-litre turbocharged petrol engine, this Corsa combines sharp looks with great fuel economy—perfect for city driving or daily commuting.
      - ✅ ULEZ compliant – drive into any city with confidence
      - ✅ Turbocharged petrol engine – great performance and economy
      - ✅ Sporty Limited Edition trim with modern tech and styling
      - Limited Edition Key Features Include:
      - • 17” Gloss Black Alloy Wheels
      - • Sports Styling Pack – Black Roof, Mirrors, and Rear Spoiler
      - • Touchscreen Infotainment System
      - • Bluetooth Connectivity and Media Streaming
      - • USB and AUX Input
      - • Cruise Control with Speed Limiter
      - • Air Conditioning
      - • Heated Front Windscreen (Quickclear)
      - • Electric Front Windows and Mirrors
      - • LED Daytime Running Lights
      - • ISOFIX Child Seat Mounts
      - • Multifunction Leather Steering Wheel
      - • Colour-Coded Bodywork and Sport Seats
      - Drives superb—smooth, powerful, and efficient. No warning lights or mechanical issues.
      - • Recently serviced and inspected
      - • MOT to be renewed at point of sale
      - ✅ Drive away today – reserve SO65 TVU with a refundable £100 deposit (subject to TandCs)
      - 🚚 Nationwide delivery available at competitive rates
      - ⸻
      - Why Buy from AW Trade Centre?
      - We provide:
      - • Full mechanical inspection
      - • Free comprehensive warranty
      - • HPI clear vehicles (unless otherwise stated)
      - • Fresh valet inside and out
      - • Friendly, honest, and pressure-free service
      - 📞 Call or message us today to arrange a viewing or reserve this Vauxhall Corsa Limited Edition.
    </Description>
    <Image>https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w800/1a710139c1384aa59b5688885efbfe52.jpg,
https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w600/7dbbdf97c2b64b2cbda4cff399a96201.jpg,
https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w600/9dc8bb7439d5489cae33df7f4019a8c9.jpg,
https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w600/79fbb467609f4da19d796a170be1b7ca.jpg,
https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w600/70e8cb3251a048999eb152c1a7de55d5.jpg,
https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w600/3b7954384ec6431c975623b29ca740da.jpg,
https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/w600/bc4c56af5c484841bf1b58940ace1a2e.jpg</Image>
  </Car>
</Cars>
