<Cars>
  <Car>
    <ID>1</ID>
    <Name>Volkswagen</Name>
    <Model>CC</Model>
    <FullModel>2.0 TDI BlueMotion Tech GT Euro 5 (s/s) 4dr</FullModel>
    <EyeCatcher>CLUTCH KIT✅6M W'NTY✅£35 R’TAX</EyeCatcher>
    <Value>4499</Value>
    <Mileage>90500</Mileage>
    <YearOfManu>2014</YearOfManu>
    <CatStat>HPI Clear</CatStat>
    <FuelType>Diesel</FuelType>
    <Transmission>Manual</Transmission>
    <Colour>Grey</Colour>
    <ExtraFeatures>12V Socket - Centre Console, Bluetooth Telephone Preparation for Hands Free Profile Enabled Telephones, Colour Screen - 5in, DAB+ - Digital Radio Reception, Dash-mounted MP3 Compatible CD Player, MDI - Multi Device Interface, RNS 315 Touch Screen Satellite Navigation and Radio System, SD Card Reader, Speakers x8, Analogue Clock, Cruise Control, Driver Alert System, Flat Tyre Indicator, Multifunction Computer - Colour, Parking Sensors - Front and Rear, Parking Sensors - Rear, Tyre Pressure Indicator, Warning Light for Low Washer Fluid, Warning Lights for Open Boot Lid and Doors, 18in Alloy Wheels - Chicago, 18in Alloy Wheels - Interlagos, Anti-Theft Wheel Bolts, Body Coloured Door Handles, Bumpers - Body Coloured Front and Bumper Strips, Door Mirrors - Body Coloured with Integrated Indicators LED, Door Mirrors - Electrically Adjustable and Heated, Electric Windows - Front and Rear, Grey exterior colour, Heated Windscreen Washer Jets, Radiator Grille - Gloss Black with Chrome Trimmed Surround and Louvres, Spare Wheel - Full Size Alloy, Tinted Glass - Heat Insulating Rear 65 Percent Light Absorbing from B Pillar Backwards, Bi-Xenon Headlights, Daytime Running Lights, Front Fog Lights, Headlight Washer System, Headlights - Automatic Range Adjustment, Headlights - Coming-Leaving Home Function, Headlights - Dusk Sensor - Automatic Driving Lights, High Level 3rd Brake Light, Rear Tail Lights and Rear Number Plate Lights - LED, 2 Zone Electronic Climate Control with Automatic Air Recirculation, Armrest - Front Centre with Storage Compartment, Automatic Dimming Rear View Mirror, Black full leather interior, Carpet Mats - Front and Rear, Cup Holders - Front x2, Cup Holders - Rear x2, Drivers Seat Height Adjustment, Front Seat Back Storage Pockets, Glovebox - Illuminated - Cooled - Lockable, Head Restraints - Front 4-Way Adjustment, Heated Front Seats, Height and Reach Adjustable Steering Column, Interior Lighting - Front and Rear with Interior Delay and Dimming Function, Intermittent Windscreen Wiper Control, Leather Trimmed Three-Spoke Steering Wheel and Gear Knob, Load Lashing Points x2 in Luggage Compartment, Load-Through Provision, Nappa Leather - Black, Press and Drive Key, Rain Sensor, Reading Lights - Front x2, Reading Lights - Rear, Rear Centre Armrest, Seats - Drivers 6-Way Electric Adjustment, Seats - Front Lumbar Support, Seats - Front Sports, Seats - Height Adjustment - Front Passenger, Seats - Split Folding Rear, Stainless Steel Door Sills - Front and Rear, Steering Wheel - Multifunction, Storage Compartment in Roof Console, Storage Compartments in Doors, Storage Tray in Centre Console, Sun Visors - Vanity Mirrors and Illuminated, Three Rear Head Restraints, Trim - Interior - Dark Brushed Aluminium Decorative Inserts in Dashboard-Centre Console and Doors, Two Rear Air Vents, Power Assisted Steering - Speed Sensitive, Suspension - Sports - Lowered by Approx 15mm, ABS - Anti-Lock Braking System, ASR - Anti Slip Regulation, Airbags - Curtain, Airbags - Driver, Airbags - Front Passenger, Airbags - Front Passenger with Deactivation Switch, Airbags - Front Seat Side Impact, Alarm with Interior Protection, BAS - Brake Assist System, Central Locking with Remote Control, Countersteer Support, Differential Lock - Electronic, Door Side Impact Protection, EBD - Electronic Brake Pressure Distribution, ESP - Electronic Stability Programme, Electronic Engine Immobiliser, Electronic Parking Brake with Auto Hold Function, Height-Adjustable Front Three-Point Seat Belts with Tensioners, Hill Hold Assist, ISOFIX Child Seat Preparation - Outer Rear, Seatbelt Reminder, Warning Triangle</ExtraFeatures>
    <Reg>VN64 AOV</Reg>
    <Video></Video>
    <MetaTag>Volkswagen CC 2.0 TDI BlueMotion Tech GT Euro 5 (s/s) 4dr Diesel Manual Grey</MetaTag>
    <Description>
      - Available now is this sleek and well-presented 2014 (64) Volkswagen CC 2.0 TDI BlueMotion Tech GT, a stylish executive coupe-saloon offering strong performance, excellent comfort, and impressive fuel economy.
      - Powered by the refined 2.0 TDI diesel engine, it delivers smooth power, strong torque, and great MPG — perfect for motorway driving, commuting, or anyone wanting executive comfort with sporty styling.
      - ✅ GT Spec • Executive Coupe Styling • Excellent MPG
      - Key Features Include:
      - • GT specification
      - • Leather interior
      - • Heated front seats
      - • Touchscreen infotainment system
      - • Satellite navigation
      - • Bluetooth and media connectivity
      - • Cruise control
      - • Dual-zone climate control
      - • Front and rear parking sensors
      - • Alloy wheels
      - • Multifunction steering wheel
      - • Electric windows and mirrors
      - • ISOFIX
      - • LED daytime running lights
      - Drives beautifully — smooth, refined, and comfortable. No warning lights or mechanical issues.
      - • Recently serviced and inspected
      - • MOT expires 03/11/2026
      - ✅ Drive away today – reserve VN64 AOV with a refundable £100 deposit (TandCs apply).
      - 🚚 Nationwide delivery available at competitive rates.
      - ⸻
      - Why Buy from AW Trade Centre?
      - We provide:
      - • Full mechanical inspection
      - • Free comprehensive warranty
      - • HPI clear vehicles (unless otherwise stated)
      - • Fresh valet inside and out
      - • Friendly, honest, and pressure-free service
      - 📞 Call or message us today to arrange a viewing or reserve this Volkswagen CC 2.0 TDI GT.
    </Description>
    <Image>https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/ed74d847a13c434d8baf7738cd559346.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/8d8b580bde1a42e1bdd4c309171d9144.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/8b56548b62584bd3a1328817fa998182.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/1a880574af1e4ff7857b740c70a6bb58.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/1697ba28d62546d48364ee16b8e6de93.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/332776d7ceb24c608cb2e32e9dad5c77.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/bb0a4d4d4c644b5aa036b71528def0a8.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/f64f5c91d0f54822aeb2bf8d5618ab39.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/8c30db268be3423eb0582800a0f1d868.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/9c7d4c4f3f9a432cbc8f1c305c2fea15.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/3cc9026b37784acb9bea7945ca2ce761.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/381f7aed7b26435bba7d4d43d58f2d7e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/b43723b067d34371af962e70361a3610.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/f67a95f287bf49eb87618ecce0e0a35e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/40a734da235647fc835d3c33ae3fb244.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/bb718284bcdb490880d066ceb8d8da01.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/0d8fca2f48e54005963ab45d4e559638.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/73bd5de0d4a54dc19f043dd3d80a6c8b.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/3b6d04dd380b4cb680dbabedb0a3478c.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/ed432e9b63e44b6683db18929a12380b.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/1e5185fd65874a8583a82edaff11d13b.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/de2048d167fe46a9ad81ccea5d2b9896.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/bb7af76d1bff4b3ebab26cdea26a754a.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/555a2c623f8148c6a8eb1041b2397234.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/ef76bb1937fd4f2688c82ec9d42f6a67.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/9f93fb8b080b43289624b6cb6fb313ae.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/124f39512e8545b3ae6afde1301329a1.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/39e20e4e25084a11b9946aa2fa9d8fff.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/1507f6d9ac204d5c93c9b73af03ecb76.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/d0a590d0b442418f8cf70785dff5f15c.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/23ca7080bf6f4dd2b5743d956f7ad1db.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/9254e49a1e884737b83083e4d70a8030.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/312c2ea1f2544f1881d9ef468d1e1a32.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/ce5dd2784df646648354302b7b58dcf3.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/dd10192b54294af7bbc05d35ab81db80.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/75b0679c56be492187f0b397f1c2193a.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/8aee488fbfed4ca4a7eb8d1fefc32dae.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/a22becacbeae4841947b077d3e04cd9c.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/288e948f767a49d99653b198e1d81551.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/ba271b777b50494dbc64a3e9688f1133.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/7093cc354c324bdd91b8aa81b078520b.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/0882215eff054e7788e19f09e71a74ec.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/7fd4f4db94a14f118d97764b69a586d2.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/fbe04a77843d4d02b8328ea1f8fbe134.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/7cbbf1f2698a4e07ba7131afaa585e3d.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/72a6c38f43e34b699a7c78d5020cb3f0.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/c41ff0b2dfd9417b96ac140e2805fa96.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/ee56d9e5b4ed4ac78735574f110d9148.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/fb5f019080ca4d87a918e4b07c4ad5ac.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/21924a44dcc1462e94783a81968d097a.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/8fc3a859f17b432b97e6da71b1f776a4.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/f809876315334781b21fa9ce8619f8bd.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/951bd16b617c48f1bac13cb00d32864d.jpg</Image>
    <Tax>£35</Tax>
    <Insurance>24E</Insurance>
    <Mpg>61.4</Mpg>
    <AT>autotrader.co.uk/car-details/202602210117186?journey=DEALER_STOCK_LIST_JOURNEY&amp;sort=price-asc&amp;twcs=true&amp;searchId=62e0f2d0-358e-41e5-96c5-0bcc97cbfb1e&amp;advertising-location=at_profile_cars&amp;advertising-location=at_cars&amp;page=1&amp;postcode=ts233ta&amp;fromsra&amp;fromDealerSearchResults&amp;backLinkQueryParams=advertising-location%3Dat_cars%26advertising-location%3Dat_profile_cars%26onesearchad%3DUsed%26onesearchad%3DNearly%2520New%26onesearchad%3DNew%26postcode%3Dts233ta%26retailerId%3D10041187%26sort%3Dprice-asc%26flrfc%3D1</AT>
  </Car>
  <Car>
    <ID>2</ID>
    <Name>Ford</Name>
    <Model>Kuga</Model>
    <FullModel>2.0 TDCi Titanium X AWD Euro 5 5dr</FullModel>
    <EyeCatcher>1YR MOT✅6M WARRANTY✅FSH✅</EyeCatcher>
    <Value>4999</Value>
    <Mileage>91200</Mileage>
    <YearOfManu>2013</YearOfManu>
    <CatStat>HPI Clear</CatStat>
    <FuelType>Diesel</FuelType>
    <Transmission>Manual</Transmission>
    <Colour>White</Colour>
    <ExtraFeatures>Bluetooth Handsfree and Voice Control, Centre Console - additional 12V power socket, Emergency Assistance, Ford SYNC, MP3 Compatibility, Portable Audio Device Connector, Sony DAB Digital Radio, Sony DAB Navigation System with Rear View Camera, Sony Radio CD with 8 Speakers - MP3 Compatible, Speakers - x8, TFT Display screen, Cruise Control with Speed Limiter, DDS - Deflation Detection System, Parking Sensor - Rear, 18in Alloy Wheels, 19in Alloy Wheels, Appearance Pack, Body Colour Exterior Mirrors, Door Handles - Body Colour, Door Lever - Aluminium, Door Mirrors - Electrically Operated and Heated, Door Mirrors - Puddle Lights, Door Mirrors with Integrated Indicators, Electric Windows - Front and Rear with One Touch, Front lower grille - Moondust Silver colour surround, Front upper grille - High-gloss black with chrome bar, Heated Front Windscreen, Heated Washer Jets, Locking Wheel Nuts, Panorama Roof, Rear Spoiler - Body Colour, Scuff plates - front moondust silver colour, Spare Wheel - Mini Steel, Tinted Glass - Green, Twin Exhaust Outlet, White exterior colour, Bi-Xenon Headlights, Front Fog Lights, Headlights - Automatic, Headlights - Courtesy Delay, Headlights - Jet Wash, Headlights - Levelling System - Automatic, LED Daytime Running Lights, Rear Lights - LED, Air Conditioning - Dual Zone Electronic Automatic Temperature Control, Automatic Dimming Rear View Mirror, Automatic Rain Sensing Wipers, Black full leather interior, Centre Console - Sliding Armrest, Courtesy Light - Footwell Illumination, Courtesy Light - Front and Rear Reading Lights, Courtesy Light - LED Overhead with Theatre Style Dimming Ambient Lighting, Drivers Seat Lumbar Support, Floor Mats - Carpet - Front, Ford Power Engine Start-Stop Button, Front Seat - Passengers Manual Lumbar Support Adjustment, Gearshift Knob - Leather, Heated Driver and Passenger Seats, Large Stowage Bin, Rear Seat - Folding Centre Armrest with 2 Integrated Cup Holders and Flip up Storage, Seats - 60-40 Rear Split Back, Seats - Drivers Manual Height and Fore-Aft Adjustment, Seats - Front Sports, Steering Column - Rake and Reach Adjustment, Steering Wheel - 4 Spoke Leather Trimmed, Steering Wheel - Multifunction, Storage - Upper Instrument Panel, Stowage Pockets - Front Seatback, Torino Leather - Charcoal Black, Variable Dimming of Instrument Cluster and Radio Screen Display, EPAS - Electric Power Assisted Steering, Front suspension - Independent with MacPherson Struts, Rear suspension - Independent control blade multi-link system and anti-roll bar, Variable sensitivity adjustment, Visual AWD Monitor, ABS - Anti-lock Braking System, Airbags - Drivers Knee, Airbags - Front Passenger, Airbags - Front and 2nd Row Curtain, Airbags - Side Impact, Alarm - Thatcham Category 1 with Volume Sensing and Perimeter, Bounce-Back Sensors, Drivers Airbag, EBA - Emergency Brake Assist, EBD - Electronic Brakeforce Distribution, ESP - Electronic Stability Programme, Emergency Brake Warning, Ford Easy-Fuel Capless Refuelling System, HLA - Hill Launch Assist, IPS - Intelligent Protection System, ISOFIX, Keyless Opening with Hands Free Power Tailgate, RSC - Roll Stability Control, Remote Central Locking, TSC - Trailer Stability Programme, TVC - Torque Vectoring Control, Traction Control - TC</ExtraFeatures>
    <Reg>YC13 VFZ</Reg>
    <Video></Video>
    <MetaTag>Ford Kuga 2.0 TDCi Titanium X AWD Euro 5 5dr Diesel Manual White</MetaTag>
    <Description>
      - Available now is this well-presented and high-spec 2013 Ford Kuga 2.0 TDCi Titanium X AWD, a spacious and capable SUV offering strong performance, excellent comfort, and great practicality.
      - Powered by the reliable 2.0 TDCi diesel engine paired with All-Wheel Drive, it delivers confident handling in all conditions while maintaining excellent fuel economy — perfect for family use, commuting, or long-distance driving.
      - This example benefits from full service history, showing it has been well maintained throughout its life.
      - ✅ Titanium X Spec • AWD • Full Service History
      - Key Features Include:
      - • Full panoramic sunroof
      - • Reverse camera
      - • Driver’s electric seat
      - • Sony infotainment system
      - • Full leather interior
      - • Heated front seats
      - • Satellite navigation
      - • Bluetooth and media connectivity
      - • Cruise control
      - • Dual-zone climate control
      - • Front and rear parking sensors
      - • Power folding door mirrors
      - • Alloy wheels
      - • Multifunction steering wheel
      - • Electric windows and mirrors
      - • ISOFIX
      - • Daytime running lights
      - Drives superb — smooth, powerful, and comfortable. No warning lights or mechanical issues.
      - • Recently serviced and inspected
      - • MOT expires 09/03/2027
      - ✅ Drive away today – reserve YC13 VFZ with a refundable £100 deposit (TandCs apply).
      - 🚚 Nationwide delivery available at competitive rates.
      - ⸻
      - Why Buy from AW Trade Centre?
      - We provide:
      - • Full mechanical inspection
      - • Free comprehensive warranty
      - • HPI clear vehicles (unless otherwise stated)
      - • Fresh valet inside and out
      - • Friendly, honest, and pressure-free service
      - 📞 Call or message us today to arrange a viewing or reserve this Ford Kuga 2.0 TDCi Titanium X AWD.
    </Description>
    <Image>https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/6a391045d9e54413a24c4260e8f067d1.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/0011e72f4d824d86a12c8936dcb77afe.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/709834b990e44ce78f4d298dd1893d10.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/0ad6f65770ad4c5fa8171eab01d23eb3.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/f48ddc7da1724c869ec9046d7e1287e2.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/8440056a1db24b1193ff2f5df19af4a8.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/be767bae42c2445db20a7ff471a20399.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/b0d17af2d5c049bcb98676054453c7ec.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/3e2cc35535414572b3b0c2f2f9fe1851.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/33c83b2ce94744858b5fc0a5ba44aeb6.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/aa5cd1caea594941a06d94412d95d9b6.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/c1bfcbc7a386405ab21330d2c613dff8.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/4eaa9148ee264e25a30a7db630521141.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/c09bbd3abc1e43798a4a4ddf24e0d44d.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/3ac111ee257c4bd4bb975abffe6bd684.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/107d084dfdcf4339bc2af41812984ed3.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/799090d5bf4b4689a2dd0696768b28b4.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/de8343b0dc71411cae804ab21a999ab2.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/1ff75f5a826a4df1a6ace3c15f191f10.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/9e330c7616e745f99d508677846a2f10.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/662d3a23a27d4fc9a4c77bbc254aaa56.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/40ce4b2e40bc4ff8b36ac10158d8985b.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/c4acc7e492f44dae8ae6882e32dcf797.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/f05760964ebd4d6cb5952ec7915baf2c.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/f8542f7b61914f95bde6f0a11bf7c2a6.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/d7c35e5d4e30412095bfb35d1df4d66c.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/fa5786beed874a2d8d1476cac717c9e9.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/6e1b8588822348c5b971dabd6f002513.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/39fb6869f7c64f4fb1be10afda4e8813.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/7299e3f237a7426686d503bdf32742b0.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/a7569b99172847a7b30acc963b0cec36.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/954413499889478093f598a921bd7cb9.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/0ee46fa91b604473a67611d1fdfb59e4.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/72d0175e726b40e0bde50cf71fb13bff.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/8f40de72b7c34b35a52fa45c2031fbbb.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/f18258fdaa634a35ad8d757bea45cb24.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/9a0bcdf6bd0942bf8fc6b8aff52cc656.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/3003af24ca734f848dbf38e922e11861.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/ad7d2c30a0a04221b5ac67a6d8aa12e0.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/3b37f21d73c94801bba42e599a705cbe.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/4afdc3292b984e5e8ea2200003d6de93.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/e42bdd1a7a134a41a39ea5cf8093e832.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/24fe03e8e7e74235a2e62796e9d4d7e7.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/7794cea339c34106b9c79939cdf0870c.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/b543fc4880944497b5307af859f89201.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/11290a3abfb34b7a96eddb309e0ef779.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/777b0a0ab3bd44d9b29d5e11b89ae2f5.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/7dd4f29af053458886e443b5cbfe88cb.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/17c6cfe61f764453a7cea7d723b9b8c9.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/a49b53b5772949e5b923dbdd9999c36d.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/02420de01ad840cea1cc151a2c3c9691.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/b04f68740f1d4567a7c935a32cc06fbb.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/c33475f33c964411b9d5cbe5089e43cd.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/7a557e956d004f50be2524703bfb561f.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/78bfe562031a4c96a85f715af762efbd.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/559f5fccd61e475b887f970be49a657e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/558d11cedfc84f5297c547e7b7b80af7.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/9eba318107ff423fbffc4b570966b87a.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/99e33f8a98b840d094dacd1594bf3370.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/8d913121f7f048309dffe8b7343fa0da.jpg</Image>
    <Tax>265</Tax>
    <Insurance>24E</Insurance>
    <Mpg>47.9</Mpg>
    <AT>https://www.autotrader.co.uk/car-details/202603100587476?journey=DEALER_STOCK_LIST_JOURNEY&amp;sort=price-asc&amp;twcs=true&amp;searchId=b3e252d7-ada4-4d7c-a1d8-cbdf5c88b240&amp;advertising-location=at_profile_cars&amp;advertising-location=at_cars&amp;page=1&amp;postcode=ts233ta&amp;fromsra=&amp;fromDealerSearchResults=&amp;backLinkQueryParams=advertising-location%3Dat_cars%26advertising-location%3Dat_profile_cars%26onesearchad%3DUsed%26onesearchad%3DNearly%2520New%26onesearchad%3DNew%26postcode%3Dts233ta%26retailerId%3D10041187%26sort%3Dprice-asc%26flrfc%3D1&amp;calc-deposit=550&amp;calc-term=48&amp;calc-mileage=10000</AT>
  </Car>
  <Car>
    <ID>3</ID>
    <Name>Audi</Name>
    <Model>A4</Model>
    <FullModel>2.0 TDIe Technik Euro 5 (s/s) 4dr</FullModel>
    <EyeCatcher>PX TO CLEAR✅FULL LEATHERS✅</EyeCatcher>
    <Value>2999</Value>
    <Mileage>112400</Mileage>
    <YearOfManu>2010</YearOfManu>
    <CatStat>HPI Clear</CatStat>
    <FuelType>Diesel</FuelType>
    <Transmission>Manual</Transmission>
    <Colour>Grey</Colour>
    <ExtraFeatures>10 Speakers, Concert Radio and single CD player with MP3 facility, DVD SatNav, Mobile telephone preparation- Bluetooth interface, Grey exterior colour, Stone Grey Front grille, 4Spoke Leather Steering Wheel, Aluminium hologram inlay, Black full leather interior, Deletion of model and engine designation at Rear, Engine badge delete, FrontandRear floor mats, Multifunction Steering Wheel</ExtraFeatures>
    <Reg>SP60 XLK</Reg>
    <Video></Video>
    <MetaTag>Audi A4 2.0 TDIe Technik Euro 5 (s/s) 4dr Diesel Manual Grey</MetaTag>
    <Description>
      ⚠️ SPARES OR REPAIRS / PART EXCHANGE TO CLEAR ⚠️
      This vehicle has been taken in part exchange and is being listed as a trade sale due to its age and mileage. It is sold as seen, without warranty or guarantees. Buyers are welcome to inspect and test drive prior to purchase.
      ⸻
      Available now is this 2010 (60) Audi A4 2.0 TDIe Technik, a premium saloon offering excellent fuel economy, refined comfort, and Audi’s renowned build quality.
      Powered by the efficient 2.0 TDIe diesel engine, it delivers strong MPG and smooth motorway cruising.
      ✅ £35 road tax • TDI Efficiency • Great MPG
      Key Features Include:
      • Technik specification
      • Satellite navigation system
      • Bluetooth and media connectivity
      • Cruise control
      • Dual-zone climate control
      • Alloy wheels
      • Multifunction steering wheel
      • Electric windows and mirrors
      • Full leather seats
      • Heated seats
      • Daytime running lights
      Starts and drives (unless you want to specify faults).
      • MOT status to be confirmed
      💷 Priced to clear – no offers, no warranty.
      🚗 Drive away today – first to view will buy.
      ⸻
      📞 Call or message to arrange viewing.
    </Description>
    <Image>https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/68cd54caa0974b0f80c02ae873e6625c.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/5b249887c4e84c9fa1b22bf07a56dfab.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/2872fe19c70444c38777cc8d20bf7581.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/ed74479f87144909af26ced6b7b9fb5f.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/4b4c403ad46a467fb2e1726fa99e624e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/1b7e45778a2b4faaa4c6356c949f797d.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/a1b816c445984582a3beea60de254a2e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/466304ca9b8b49a98435f0b2b0799db5.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/c9c4ff44cdda46debee75d1cbd16bf44.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/2883d22c85d444d39b115e48a17ff56e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/5f9451b534ca4b3486e4d2632a67c1b2.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/f6934d66f2d9469ba941eb6158e953a6.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/48463eed0a534c5d8f8d9f3e42cf31d3.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/49f024399ebd45f1be0b7b8d2ced52d3.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/f0a9480decb140a49b35dc2e7817dd99.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/89c4d21f9dc440e7a24de154c754fe01.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/3e6e89b4316045b7b7a5aab06b302496.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/96e861c262f24495ad1cd3c46523b331.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/bf17cbf9bb88432a80163a218b98fcdd.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/ed9e3ac2194d495ba116a971e10a053e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/71ad261c944b4a68a77327c0299b0b3a.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/a57a036b7496474d8ec91521852c4de4.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/2e32a0d5ba5246c886597c678e766b72.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/b44100c01ed34074a6cf5d016ea3e0ac.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/0d9b7c945c8446baa9b89b7e9452466d.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/928d3e48b6f24412ad0e428a7470b226.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/9b5895da5997428aa53fdc79ff2b9d44.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/e897d30ea91a49c2ab5c2b6a93acc301.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/ec95f5cb8ffb4c3ebb57cf9cbd244dc2.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/6664383d1b6b4eda964ee67a811c0768.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/52d701ef93a64a4db53332dd7404729e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/b368128aa049474ea53f162781d1b354.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/f34b852c738e479a8ee5c0e12c91a42b.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/e5d22c053d724815b462ae7044583d27.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/0fdf596aa40a43e0908c4f1fbd237451.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/551295ce067f418ab13e602bca888c8d.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/d559e010694e4997acf11e646c6d2ddb.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/ffbfcc8e2f07454eb90a7dcaf8d55c40.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/afa453345313458187d91480d8d7b9cb.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/30f791645f614f7ca717f89f9ddd775b.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/2ce9a1819b4c4ad4a4b044d92a8dae4a.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/9be2648e51f64f3890e3d693ffbb5bde.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/406145c9ab294e768272789d5e145493.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/26f737c43ffb47838dd1b111b3970d6d.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/f162e09f58684caea393b4c5f871abdb.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/c7b48abfaff0433f8ba41936f46fe6ab.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/64f22e3514024f5d9eeef4179fe9e961.jpg</Image>
    <Tax>35</Tax>
    <Insurance>22E</Insurance>
    <Mpg>61.4</Mpg>
    <AT>https://www.autotrader.co.uk/car-details/202603251010436?journey=DEALER_STOCK_LIST_JOURNEY&amp;sort=price-asc&amp;twcs=true&amp;searchId=780d43e5-2f23-44a7-ba3f-07f257f5d1ce&amp;advertising-location=at_profile_cars&amp;advertising-location=at_cars&amp;page=1&amp;postcode=ts233ta&amp;fromsra=&amp;fromDealerSearchResults=&amp;backLinkQueryParams=advertising-location%3Dat_cars%26advertising-location%3Dat_profile_cars%26onesearchad%3DUsed%26onesearchad%3DNearly%2520New%26onesearchad%3DNew%26postcode%3Dts233ta%26retailerId%3D10041187%26sort%3Dprice-asc%26flrfc%3D1&amp;calc-deposit=300&amp;calc-term=48&amp;calc-mileage=10000</AT>
  </Car>
  <Car>
    <ID>4</ID>
    <Name>Volkswagen</Name>
    <Model>Polo</Model>
    <FullModel>1.6 TDI SE Euro 5 5dr</FullModel>
    <EyeCatcher>T-BELT✅£35 R-TAX✅6M WARRANTY✅</EyeCatcher>
    <Value>3999</Value>
    <Mileage>62000</Mileage>
    <YearOfManu>2010</YearOfManu>
    <CatStat>HPI Clear</CatStat>
    <FuelType>Diesel</FuelType>
    <Transmission>Manual</Transmission>
    <Colour>Grey</Colour>
    <ExtraFeatures>RCD 310 dash- mounted MP3 Compatible CD player with 6 Speakers and aux- for connection to external Media source, Trip computer, 15in Castille Alloy Wheels with AntiTheft Wheel bolts, Grey exterior colour, Air Conditioning, Black cloth interior</ExtraFeatures>
    <Reg>CK10 YAE</Reg>
    <Video></Video>
    <MetaTag>Volkswagen Polo 1.6 TDI SE Euro 5 5dr Diesel Manual Grey</MetaTag>
    <Description>
      Available now is this economical and well-presented 2010 Volkswagen Polo 1.6 TDI SE, a reliable hatchback offering excellent fuel economy, solid build quality, and great everyday practicality.
      Powered by the efficient 1.6 TDI diesel engine, it delivers strong MPG, smooth driving, and low running costs — ideal for commuting or long-distance use.
      ✅ £35 yearly road tax • Excellent MPG • Low running costs
      Key Features Include:
      • Rear parking sensors
      • SE specification
      • Air conditioning
      • Cruise control
      • Bluetooth and media connectivity (if fitted)
      • Alloy wheels
      • Multifunction steering wheel
      • Electric windows and mirrors
      • Remote central locking
      • ISOFIX
      • Trip computer
      Drives great — smooth, comfortable, and very economical. No warning lights or mechanical issues.
      • Recently serviced and inspected
      • MOT to be renewed at point of sale
      ✅ Drive away today – reserve CK10 YAE with a refundable £100 deposit (TandCs apply).
      🚚 Nationwide delivery available at competitive rates.
      ⸻
      Why Buy from AW Trade Centre?
      We provide:
      • Full mechanical inspection
      • Free comprehensive warranty
      • HPI clear vehicles (unless otherwise stated)
      • Fresh valet inside and out
      • Friendly, honest, and pressure-free service
      📞 Call or message us today to arrange a viewing or reserve this Volkswagen Polo 1.6 TDI SE.
    </Description>
    <Image>https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/67f43d30a9e044b988097808e53a1520.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/a10172eafa5a47ab99d0a24b4398eff3.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/da4122ca0bb14b40a58be36939603174.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/ce8860d733c648b2a95a282094a6a799.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/5b937c2df98541afa9896bf7c6c66c4f.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/622d50e1c80d4e96a3624c6882fe725c.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/c186397561f044689cc6b9ea1ed002e3.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/f9aa52911c41474080f90e1362555c58.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/e49edce4e5f147f5a3024a21f950d35c.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/c5ff3212d578421eb29457743cba8ce4.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/928b0bcfa9104a2699f14681d4aa7bc8.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/8c6a41591138460ea43d2b31f8ea749b.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/2080201ac40846e3b20e7dc1b8a29742.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/1abd8e7f63824e0b9e5d282ab40d96c9.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/a5d6638e720d4818b4fcd57d04d2e845.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/bda1d32b5e8a48269a6caba8a38c636c.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/bc4e55f58fa549999fe16e83cc10dcc5.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/ecc4813b4cbf497fa4459b6c67bd099b.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/b741326096834bddaf77263a7e8cc94d.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/ba562f93ec034e2ab16847f5fb77abe8.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/519a1eb1c5a042cd8e653d9e4cce932a.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/7fb09e3c824b4ce5a68317ac95256cd1.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/d379d73740774d15879eff0998adf2cc.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/fd1cf80d97e24adeb0df07c607cb93f7.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/f4b139b1938e4a29a8ef759a64df13ae.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/dc322a34689e401497c273a9f3731555.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/d958cb35717945c28988deecc7dcc97d.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/9042f0a780d24c91a4b88aca9c9eedb2.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/f2b7cf2f42524d6eb8c5f440408e22ff.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/18dea073fbb2466386afac4e9fc1ce7c.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/1526e7137da8401ba7c3ef5afdebb1e2.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/1acac572d5394552839a60f75a53b868.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/630a8b7a2fc84e6ebadc7865b887dc3f.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/ffdaae32fa1d45c19a415cab19085178.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/2968752fb9b9436daffd87a755e4756e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/10046aa455ae494dbfb5c7ebbda921b6.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/22559cdb8f3647a58461f1f82362c9ac.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/e07a577aad9543059aade3a9fe8b979c.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/4e8984a64bdd4dd3b053b64fad9c2903.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/ec83c621bb404739808c48f0a5645dbc.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/d21d6000a15d4db799282f447c99afe4.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/e14d01b86d15424eb777dfd39171d1dc.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/e77256cad92e416392a15407195de711.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/fd035d74fba149579054a9173e990838.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/381c1e4b7c15467a96e4c0442684a0ce.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/14027087291e4435afb589302d9b0548.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/56657d160fdd4d16a93e9a61a1336dff.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/9bdf90099bfb4e13b97e9dd12a9662cf.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/ac63a3adf3024d6a972ab43ee0a42cc4.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/7dd2ccd5f38e431db0c099e3ad54ff36.jpg</Image>
    <Tax>35</Tax>
    <Insurance>10E</Insurance>
    <Mpg>67.3</Mpg>
    <AT>https://www.autotrader.co.uk/car-details/202603261038434?journey=DEALER_STOCK_LIST_JOURNEY&amp;sort=price-asc&amp;twcs=true&amp;searchId=f18b3424-0e4e-4f42-9f08-e2ba1fbe9d6d&amp;advertising-location=at_profile_cars&amp;advertising-location=at_cars&amp;page=1&amp;postcode=ts233ta&amp;fromsra=&amp;fromDealerSearchResults=&amp;backLinkQueryParams=advertising-location%3Dat_cars%26advertising-location%3Dat_profile_cars%26onesearchad%3DUsed%26onesearchad%3DNearly%2520New%26onesearchad%3DNew%26postcode%3Dts233ta%26retailerId%3D10041187%26sort%3Dprice-asc%26flrfc%3D1&amp;calc-deposit=400&amp;calc-term=48&amp;calc-mileage=10000</AT>
  </Car>
  <Car>
    <ID>5</ID>
    <Name>Ford</Name>
    <Model>Fiesta</Model>
    <FullModel>1.4 Titanium 5dr</FullModel>
    <EyeCatcher>AUTO✅6M WARRANTY✅DELIVERY✅ULEZ</EyeCatcher>
    <Value>3999</Value>
    <Mileage>98400</Mileage>
    <YearOfManu>2009</YearOfManu>
    <CatStat>HPI Clear</CatStat>
    <FuelType>Petrol</FuelType>
    <Transmission>Automatic</Transmission>
    <Colour>Red</Colour>
    <ExtraFeatures>2 Front Speakers, ATC Air Conditioning, Auto Wipers, Auto Wipers inc. Auto Headlamps, Carpet Mats, Cruise Control, Driver Seat Height Adjust, Heated Rear Screen, Leather Gearknob, Leather Steering Wheel, Privacy Glass, QuickClear Heated Windscreen, Quickclear Heated Windscreen, Radio/CD, MP3 Compatible with 2-Line Display and Aux In, Reach and Rake Steering Wheel, Remote Control for Audio, Split Rear Seats, Trip Computer, Upholstery Cloth, Windows - Power Front One-Shot, 16in - Alloy Wheels, Alloy Wheels - 16in 7 Spoke Titanium, Body Colour Rear Spoiler, Bumpers - Body Colour, Door Mirrors - Electrically - Operated and Heated, Power Foldable, Metallic Paint, Metallic Paint - Hot Magenta, Rear Wash/Wipe, Red exterior colour, Second Remote Ignition Key, Spare Wheel - 14in x 5.5 Steel Wheel, Black cloth interior, Map Reading Lights/Aesthetic Lighting, ESP with Traction Assist and EBA, Airbag - Driver, Airbag - Driver Seat Head Thorax, Airbag - Front Passenger, Airbag - Front Side, Airbag - Knee Driver, Anti-Lock Brakes (ABS) and Emergency Brake Distribution (EBD), Auto Headlamps, Centre Rear Seat Belt, Electronic Brake Force Distribution (EBD), Front Fog Lights, Head Restraints Front/Rear, Immobiliser, Parking Sensor - Rear, Perimeter Alarm, Power - Assisted Steering, Premier Alarm, Remote Double Locking, Third Brake Light, Tyre Mobility Kit</ExtraFeatures>
    <Reg>NG09 HJK</Reg>
    <Video></Video>
    <MetaTag>Ford Fiesta 1.4 Titanium 5dr Petrol Automatic Red</MetaTag>
    <Description>
      Available now is this well-presented and highly sought-after 2009 Ford Fiesta 1.4 Titanium Automatic, a practical and reliable hatchback offering smooth driving, great comfort, and ease of use.
      Powered by the dependable 1.4 petrol engine paired with a fully automatic gearbox, this car is perfect for those wanting a stress-free driving experience — ideal for city driving, new drivers, or anyone specifically looking for an automatic.
      ✅ AUTOMATIC • Easy to drive • Low running costs
      Key Features Include:
      • Automatic transmission
      • Titanium specification
      • Alloy wheels
      • Air conditioning
      • Bluetooth and media connectivity
      • Heated front windscreen
      • Multifunction steering wheel
      • Electric windows and mirrors
      • Remote central locking
      • ISOFIX
      • Trip computer
      Drives great — smooth, comfortable, and effortless thanks to the automatic gearbox. No warning lights or mechanical issues.
      • Recently serviced and inspected
      • MOT expires 03/02/2027
      ✅ Drive away today – reserve NG09 HJK with a refundable £100 deposit (TandCs apply).
      🚚 Nationwide delivery available at competitive rates.
      ⸻
      Why Buy from AW Trade Centre?
      We provide:
      • Full mechanical inspection
      • Free comprehensive warranty
      • HPI clear vehicles (unless otherwise stated)
      • Fresh valet inside and out
      • Friendly, honest, and pressure-free service
      📞 Call or message us today to arrange a viewing or reserve this Ford Fiesta 1.4 Titanium Automatic.
    </Description>
    <Image>https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/dc148c3add8a4bc695c4d2055f05f396.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/5bdadeea527144c4b46f84cf36839a27.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/80338b14fb2c43cd976786b7ff37cfd0.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/824d5527bbd64757877b17130f74b91b.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/1621f99e0f1e4543a688cd9c973eddfa.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/93718e70ff5f419ba28808a3e6cc216e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/1b1d63ab99a34814b1af2b8032adf554.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/fb06612e5ddb4e47976a2c95aa4e1497.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/57eafe5e29f54c0290e891f527f9c234.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/c07f811cc90d44268bbb5211e0c30776.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/9f53496f957440ec96c65fb0eeda1091.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/40a021d251c94e5ca4f29d9f8d34626b.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/367dff755f414f41985b2f1dcc04e876.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/2c32ad2bcaf14e5c8b7166e853554f34.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/5a59244ad9e54f7dbbfb473b8a5877c8.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/a1a90f1f18604d6795d539513497d585.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/eeb8a972aafe40ceb99935342e2a603f.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/0e8c1565dd6946b19a24284ef66a8090.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/70c363929cbf485c82e1482f27c0b220.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/ad065639f8e149a1952f137d8e41cf79.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/f651ade95bdf4552a1ac09102042bd1b.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/e86f36d53fe148f4855f567ed1adb40b.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/dbe6b481d0ae458b96b33f837f3b2f76.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/3e28ed2970ba485bbf56cac02415475f.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/35fa05ec5dfa4e2c83291ec25c61897e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/d794c36baab84400861e17f01a96a1de.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/ce01d388fe00478d82761e51790f7179.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/5be4a880d73e4c1e8d83c34d81281ff7.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/07bc667caf9745c3843c9397855771b7.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/88d7161a52384240a6535fc2cb2d886e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/d37d1907e35b42c7ba6616c1345c3c4a.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/d0f80b15a49a430eb801a732c9334aa6.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/64e23bcf11a841139304230c4cad402c.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/30b942e500d843e982d00280b2cbe7fa.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/39df977dffa14604bd4645c16d42452d.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/d676b729261a49f3a37c17461297774b.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/c9a4600eb0a74845bed706f849257a8d.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/fe67fd5e70594e6f8d6a3f578140be3f.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/f038e0fa3d8642c5b1d9ff5ae857ba6a.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/2c680fc4caff4b76a93c82ccd3623d6f.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/69daedac70d94dda81664dcf891af566.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/b22b25dae8b444eba05d98770c7903ff.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/f38fd184624f49dcb154d3a55697bca6.jpg</Image>
    <Tax>265</Tax>
    <Insurance>09E</Insurance>
    <Mpg></Mpg>
    <AT></AT>
  </Car>
  <Car>
    <ID>6</ID>
    <Name>Ford</Name>
    <Model>Fiesta</Model>
    <FullModel>1.4 TDCi Zetec 5dr</FullModel>
    <EyeCatcher>READ DESC✅LOW MILEAGE✅£20 RTAX</EyeCatcher>
    <Value>1200</Value>
    <Mileage>103400</Mileage>
    <YearOfManu>2008</YearOfManu>
    <CatStat>HPI Clear</CatStat>
    <FuelType>Diesel</FuelType>
    <Transmission>Manual</Transmission>
    <Colour>Blue</Colour>
    <ExtraFeatures>2 Front Speakers, Air Conditioning, Driver Seat Height Adjust, Heated Rear Screen, Leather Gearknob, Leather Steering Wheel, QuickClear Heated Windscreen, Quickclear Heated Windscreen, Radio/CD, MP3 Compatible with 2-Line Display and Aux In, Reach and Rake Steering Wheel, Remote Control for Audio, Split Rear Seats, Trip Computer, Upholstery Cloth, Windows - Power Front One-Shot, 16in - Alloy Wheels, Blue exterior colour, Body Colour Rear Spoiler, Bumpers - Body Colour, Power Heated Mirrors, Rear Wash/Wipe, Blue cloth interior, Map Reading Lights/Aesthetic Lighting, Airbag - Driver, Airbag - Driver Seat Head Thorax, Airbag - Front Passenger, Airbag - Front Side, Airbag - Knee Driver, Anti-Lock Brakes (ABS) and Emergency Brake Distribution (EBD), Centre Rear Seat Belt, Electronic Brake Force Distribution (EBD), Front Fog Lights, Head Restraints Front/Rear, Immobiliser, Power - Assisted Steering, Remote Double Locking, Third Brake Light, Tyre Mobility Kit</ExtraFeatures>
    <Reg>NV58 AUE</Reg>
    <Video></Video>
    <MetaTag>Ford Fiesta 1.4 TDCi Zetec 5dr Diesel Manual Blue</MetaTag>
    <Description>
      ✅✅PART EX TO CLEAR✅✅
      STARTS AND DRIVES AMAZING BUT HAS NOT BEEN THROUGH OUR REGULAR PREP/ INSPECTION.
      £1000 BELOW RETAIL VALUATION. IF YOU WANT THE VEHICLE PREPPED WE CAN DISCUSS THIS.
      ONLY £20 ANNUAL ROAD TAX
      - ZETEC
      - ALLOY WHEELS
      - HEATED FRONT AND REAR SCREENS
      - MULTIFUNCTIONAL STEERING WHEEL
      - RADIO AND CD PLAYER
      ANY INSPECTIONS ARE WELCOME
    </Description>
    <Image>https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/d33e66b0591f4e90b195a0bc1aa0d6ea.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/4ca84bac94104dc6bc932bf4c50a4cb0.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/f115d700878d49cfbbe3735562b5980f.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/22d50bd15be94a98863b92f951732b99.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/d2a851ad570b4cc5acf8a12ae4ae06a1.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/d7dc078d429e44b7b60dbc3e3669e177.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/be59c71c06364554b7ab1f477826968e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/cdaa2c46588e4c05b0c0d040caecba03.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/bc6eba75dfdc46b4b873a7409b848c4d.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/875c5212dffc4537a67f0f868bf6465a.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/1f70d1afff01402ea380d1bc0b0141f3.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/293c1015a4e74639be55bd7cc0f3e3b2.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/8023c1aa156c498394684b187d3fb512.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/2c8ce76f14a04734b583cdd6ea17b46b.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/8bf39fbe3134484dbdb3420d4d5f46e4.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/d36651841e6040478b950366aa3b8d58.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/30d6322223664b0abf8dcb1adeb9eede.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/81a1c6c8c61c43389b9a884e063fc522.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/4d65406561144610aa890d0b32584812.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/b3fc7cdbe5d849eb9ab7f123ff767408.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/b7fe29ad9eaa45fdb2f8f83374c2ab53.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/cf9cba0025024ef8b9a28eaeb44451ce.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/992f8c890ae6417c88e65e0461da327e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/b0e727b410684d2693daea69b4e945ef.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/93fa5d8817714ca197bbd829f085c4f6.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/9ca595027ad844bd88935f50a23c9e5f.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/b4b4c30d19c046ce8d785a5a4e2421f8.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/cab2ef745095409588a12b474165c782.jpg</Image>
    <Tax>20</Tax>
    <Insurance>10E</Insurance>
    <Mpg>67.3</Mpg>
    <AT>https://www.autotrader.co.uk/car-details/202604011202240?journey=DEALER_STOCK_LIST_JOURNEY&amp;sort=price-asc&amp;twcs=true&amp;searchId=d75ed5bf-94b1-4a19-a05c-3812ff849553&amp;advertising-location=at_profile_cars&amp;advertising-location=at_cars&amp;page=1&amp;postcode=ts233ta&amp;fromsra=&amp;fromDealerSearchResults=&amp;backLinkQueryParams=advertising-location%3Dat_cars%26advertising-location%3Dat_profile_cars%26onesearchad%3DUsed%26onesearchad%3DNearly%2520New%26onesearchad%3DNew%26postcode%3Dts233ta%26retailerId%3D10041187%26sort%3Dprice-asc%26flrfc%3D1&amp;calc-deposit=120&amp;calc-term=48&amp;calc-mileage=10000</AT>
  </Car>
  <Car>
    <ID>7</ID>
    <Name>Volkswagen</Name>
    <Model>Golf</Model>
    <FullModel>1.6 TDI S Euro 5 5dr</FullModel>
    <EyeCatcher>6M WARRANTY✅£35 R’TAX✅ALLOYS✅</EyeCatcher>
    <Value>2499</Value>
    <Mileage>97500</Mileage>
    <YearOfManu>2010</YearOfManu>
    <CatStat>HPI Clear</CatStat>
    <FuelType>Diesel</FuelType>
    <Transmission>Manual</Transmission>
    <Colour>Black</Colour>
    <ExtraFeatures>RCD 210 Radio and mp3 single CD player with 4 Speakers, 15in Steel Wheels, Black exterior colour, Air Conditioning Climatic semi Automatic Control, Black cloth interior, Delete Air Conditioning, Multifunction computer- Midline</ExtraFeatures>
    <Reg>NL10 YVJ</Reg>
    <Video></Video>
    <MetaTag>Volkswagen Golf 1.6 TDI S Euro 5 5dr Diesel Manual Black</MetaTag>
    <Description>
      Available now is this economical and reliable 2010 Volkswagen Golf 1.6 TDI S, a well-built hatchback offering excellent fuel economy, solid German build quality, and great everyday practicality.
      Powered by the efficient 1.6 TDI diesel engine, it delivers strong MPG, smooth driving, and low running costs — making it ideal for commuting or long-distance use.
      ✅ £35 road tax • Excellent MPG • Low running costs
      Key Features Include:
      • S specification
      • Air conditioning
      • Cruise control
      • Bluetooth and media connectivity (if fitted)
      • Electric windows and mirrors
      • Remote central locking
      • ISOFIX
      • Trip computer
      • Daytime running lights
      Drives great — smooth, comfortable, and very economical. No warning lights or mechanical issues.
      • Recently serviced and inspected
      • MOT expires 25/02/2027
      ✅ Drive away today – reserve NL10 YVJ with a refundable £100 deposit (TandCs apply).
      🚚 Nationwide delivery available at competitive rates.
      ⸻
      Why Buy from AW Trade Centre?
      We provide:
      • Full mechanical inspection
      • Free comprehensive warranty
      • HPI clear vehicles (unless otherwise stated)
      • Fresh valet inside and out
      • Friendly, honest, and pressure-free service
      📞 Call or message us today to arrange a viewing or reserve this Volkswagen Golf 1.6 TDI S.
    </Description>
    <Image>https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/c75745c8d92d4b07b306dac08c86a1ed.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/289472b75c5d41159c711d3739f29682.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/8dc1bafa91be47cdb16d702d507a7534.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/c592b3dac0d74d46be14991b062d70bc.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/970ff86b83b94bc8920c621bea62ca82.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/715f081efdfe46c48fac234bd91d9fff.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/addb55e92bd2452b9555e6db08bd43b6.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/058e3eeaff564ca68582a4c7ea07eef0.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/06f2b5e4f3264f68892dcfe691a685b8.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/25f31bf911824a31a66925bf4f11469e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/69bf2bc3cfcb4d1680b89b52436b265e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/1ed364993510486c862cb6b8f4bc7478.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/2a951115d16d495ca50694183f237bc3.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/23539cb0f8974a1a92be154346c5bc57.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/72c70a6f0f3c4938a6532fee868a19e3.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/027ab639c16b425186985b19efe3e771.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/7feaae9a632d41f98f4f28c69afc4872.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/afd234fd028b4d09b124b3c2172f2060.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/69d932aa0c424d07861afff4c7969717.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/ca8f24d3524648af9b9f4da58172a7f1.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/f2043faeadfa44fea76f2e6c3869a1f5.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/c11c360b20d24efd9b7addc68baa1944.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/6d5a638470be4c0599732bf540cfac03.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/bf8460720b8e48b49cf79ae2b488fe2b.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/e91992684b4d4d23b0810cef3e1716fd.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/251b59fc34c54af8b3d3babb246d1ff0.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/db41069b383d42e59d7526c85905bf3f.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/e6314450f86f4f79ae76b80df8b5771d.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/75a83256c323426ba938153ff3edb0d7.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/3cec206216c34f9db96ac5e435b1bed1.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/0036a73cf95b4e6b9bc8b9aee365bdff.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/48b2d609211b4b699505f60620b362cc.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/f44c4b88e43248d786c63941777f8196.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/9088a07246af4a509fc55a594a00ef81.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/2dc9640344d84613a12abf744c7c4ae1.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/425fae501db447579028613660996e5c.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/4fdfb0fe134743dca0ccd4401287af87.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/ef1e361fb7874cfe9556506f27b2af32.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/f9f132a49537488cae9e3bb8d61f4f1f.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/36649a34eb764b499d46c5b85fac6967.jpg</Image>
    <Tax>35</Tax>
    <Insurance>15E</Insurance>
    <Mpg>62.8</Mpg>
    <AT>https://www.autotrader.co.uk/car-details/202604041292281?journey=DEALER_STOCK_LIST_JOURNEY&amp;sort=price-asc&amp;twcs=true&amp;searchId=78f50698-57c4-40cc-906c-2e144c1c4171&amp;advertising-location=at_profile_cars&amp;advertising-location=at_cars&amp;page=1&amp;postcode=ts233ta&amp;fromsra=&amp;fromDealerSearchResults=&amp;backLinkQueryParams=advertising-location%3Dat_cars%26advertising-location%3Dat_profile_cars%26flrfc%3D1%26onesearchad%3DUsed%26onesearchad%3DNearly%2520New%26onesearchad%3DNew%26postcode%3Dts233ta%26retailerId%3D10041187%26sort%3Dprice-asc&amp;calc-deposit=250&amp;calc-term=48&amp;calc-mileage=10000</AT>
  </Car>
  <Car>
    <ID>8</ID>
    <Name>Volkswagen</Name>
    <Model>Polo</Model>
    <FullModel>1.2 TDI Match Edition Euro 5 5dr</FullModel>
    <EyeCatcher>CLUTCH KIT✅FULL MOT✅SERVICE</EyeCatcher>
    <Value>4499</Value>
    <Mileage>78300</Mileage>
    <YearOfManu>2013</YearOfManu>
    <CatStat>HPI Clear</CatStat>
    <FuelType>Diesel</FuelType>
    <Transmission>Manual</Transmission>
    <Colour>White</Colour>
    <ExtraFeatures>Bluetooth Connection - Touch Phone Kit, DAB+ - Digital Radio Reception, MDI - Multi Device Interface, RCD 310 Radio - MP3 Compatible CD Player, Cruise Control, Multifunction Computer, Parking Sensors - Rear, Tyre Pressure Indicator, 15in Alloy Wheels - Castille, Body Coloured Bumpers, Body Coloured Side Sills, Body-Coloured Door Mirrors with Integrated Indicators, Door Mirrors - Electrically Adjustable and Heated, Electric Windows - Front and Rear, Full Size Steel Spare Wheel, Heated Rear Windscreen - Automatically Switches Off, Load Lip Protective Shield, Radiator Grille - Gloss Black with Chrome Trimmed Louvre, Tinted Glass - Heat Insulating Rear 65 Percent Light Absorbing from B Pillar Backwards, White exterior colour, Daytime Running Lights, Front Fog Lights, Headlights - Halogen Clear - Range Adjustable, High Level 3rd Brake Light, Air Conditioning - Manual, Air Vent Surrounds - Matt Chrome, Centre Console with Open Storage and 12V Socket with Cover, Cup Holders - Front x2, Drivers Seat Height Adjustment, Dust and Pollen Filter, Front Seat Back Storage Pockets, Glovebox, Grab Handles - Front x2 Rear x2 with Coat Hooks, Head Restraints - Front Whiplash Optimised, Heating and Ventilation System with 4 Speed Fan and Air Recirculation Switch, Height and Reach Adjustable Steering Column, Instrument Lighting - White Adjustable Panel Illumination, Interior Lighting Delay, Luggage Compartment - Hooks, Luggage Compartment Cover - Removable, Luggage Compartment Light, Matt Chrome - Gear Lever Gaiter Surround, Matt Chrome - Handbrake Grip Button, Matt Chrome - Internal Door Handles, Reading Lights - Front x2 and Rear x1, Split Folding Rear Backrests 60-40, Storage Compartment Light, Storage Compartment in Rear Doors, Storage Compartments in Front Doors, Sun Visors - Vanity Mirrors and Illuminated, Three Rear Head Restraints, Three-Spoke Steering Wheel, Variable Boot Floor, Power Assisted Steering - Speed Sensitive, ABS - Anti-Lock Braking System, ASR - Anti Slip Regulation, Airbags - Driver, Airbags - Front Passenger, Airbags - Side Head and Thorax for Front Passenger, Alarm with Interior Protection, Central Locking - Remote with 2 Remote Keys, Differential Lock - Electronic, ESP - Electronic Stability Programme, Electronic Engine Immobiliser, HBA - Hydraulic Brake Assist, ISOFIX Child Seat Preparation for 2 Rear Seats, Seatbelt Reminder</ExtraFeatures>
    <Reg>ND13 MZO</Reg>
    <Video></Video>
    <MetaTag>Volkswagen Polo 1.2 TDI Match Edition Euro 5 5dr Diesel Manual White</MetaTag>
    <Description>
      Available now is this clean and economical Volkswagen Polo 1.2 TDI — a reliable and efficient hatchback offering low running costs, solid build quality, and a smooth everyday driving experience.
      Will come with 6 months warranty.
      ✅ Excellent fuel economy
      ✅ Cheap to tax and insure
      ✅ Ideal first car or daily runaround
      ✅ Starts and drives spot on
      ✅ Smooth gearbox and clutch
      ✅ Well maintained example
      Key Features
      • Comfortable cloth interior
      • Air conditioning
      • Electric windows
      • Electric mirrors
      • CD/Radio system
      • AUX connectivity
      • ISOFIX
      • Central locking
      • Power steering
      Driving Experience:
      Drives exactly as it should — smooth, economical, and easy to handle. Engine pulls well, gearbox is responsive, and the car is comfortable both in town and on longer journeys.
      No warning lights or mechanical issues. A dependable and practical car that’s ready to go.
      Condition
      Clean example for its age. Bodywork is tidy with only minor age-related marks, and the interior has been well kept.
      Purchase Options
      ✅ Drive away today
      💳 Reserve with a refundable £100 deposit (TandCs apply)
      🚚 Nationwide delivery available at competitive rates
      Why Buy from AW Trade Centre?
      • Full mechanical inspection
      • Free comprehensive warranty
      • HPI clear vehicles (unless stated)
      • Fresh valet inside and out
      • Friendly, honest, no-pressure service
      📞 Call or message now to arrange a viewing or secure this Volkswagen Polo 1.2 TDI 🚗
    </Description>
    <Image>https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/bcacbed932254606b06e341121be6776.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/b8258ff40c1042719dfb43a7b0732b46.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/3ca92076e1d14954bde470903b5ae57c.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/9756f211d18e4122843dfc4c7d111bfe.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/098691e57c6a436d81c2b11460398f5d.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/db10aabef7004087801052a79ed358f1.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/e3c0e9cd13384d5da154d8989eefa800.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/be4a0fea3da04237a16a8bc39a4da7ba.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/67b0c9c0216b4b3c98bc0fce5f3bb70c.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/f286ebf3d56644beb3fb382746c7a57f.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/09e196ca5922434aa85407a9fa03d2ae.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/7ce1c83e48204d7883d3aa015b160b1d.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/c4c90b73d4ca4f9db7f1aeaa71d12870.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/bf24008d6e3d4d489c7083c144324876.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/90ee8d5d5f7c49c5b42181d9aa0440c7.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/a640246db5934841b7727e2126c70813.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/bc24be7a699a4c818c72027e5eb39876.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/a8d8baa013f242afa49cd6ff21f4a291.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/58db7c98fe7d41db9a709f1278e00224.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/aaeb97a6646d4628abeee75fbeb4ee5a.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/1d68a78ce3e6429ba2b2a8593f2684bb.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/e54dff90e44947d3a1e403d982744292.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/3c7c2460ae29474abaa0166d8f140af6.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/3fde545bdfc342c39b30953a3ea62803.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/eb3dc9436a5745d1a62264f66b4c6396.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/099318e4e67a41fcac1adea581afecae.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/71eff16fc6a24787be2ff9350b0e28a2.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/762a1a22c2bf49eb9d0f89c33658320e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/3ecdc81b651848969edc00aa6247328e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/9fc34940c0774aa2bf33532df6cde95c.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/a9f24d694e104a319166677f61913323.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/8b9f323aa3bc4434bbcc7d95ccfb4edb.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/5bf8d70bf7e449e2803fcb5e4e91fc69.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/33598e38dafa4a18898a84ca59e3f79c.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/a6c5d5313f7a4b8caaf81c7072ecf2da.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/9b13fb495c284a01a7b4a4d7dafba405.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/c576235e0de14394b7da465bc40c3007.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/32e56b1771b441c88528b15b00b85b98.jpg</Image>
    <Tax>20</Tax>
    <Insurance>09E</Insurance>
    <Mpg>72.4</Mpg>
    <AT>https://www.autotrader.co.uk/car-details/202603271081049?journey=DEALER_STOCK_LIST_JOURNEY&amp;sort=price-asc&amp;twcs=true&amp;searchId=a7b1990a-3d0d-4b09-aec4-6595e7680e19&amp;advertising-location=at_profile_cars&amp;advertising-location=at_cars&amp;page=1&amp;postcode=ts233ta&amp;fromsra=&amp;fromDealerSearchResults=&amp;backLinkQueryParams=advertising-location%3Dat_cars%26advertising-location%3Dat_profile_cars%26flrfc%3D1%26onesearchad%3DUsed%26onesearchad%3DNearly%2520New%26onesearchad%3DNew%26postcode%3Dts233ta%26retailerId%3D10041187%26sort%3Dprice-asc&amp;calc-deposit=450&amp;calc-term=48&amp;calc-mileage=10000</AT>
  </Car>
  <Car>
    <ID>9</ID>
    <Name>Mercedes-Benz</Name>
    <Model>C Class</Model>
    <FullModel>2.1 C250 CDI BlueEfficiency AMG Sport Plus G-Tronic+ Euro 5 (s/s) 4dr</FullModel>
    <EyeCatcher>CARPLAY✅12M MOT✅READY TO GO</EyeCatcher>
    <Value>4499</Value>
    <Mileage>116000</Mileage>
    <YearOfManu>2012</YearOfManu>
    <CatStat>HPI Clear</CatStat>
    <FuelType>Diesel</FuelType>
    <Transmission>Automatic</Transmission>
    <Colour>White</Colour>
    <ExtraFeatures>Bluetooth Interface for Hands-Free Telephone, ATTENTION Assist, Cruise Control, Parktronic - Front with Advanced Parking Guidance, Parktronic - Rear with Advanced Parking Guidance, Tyre Pressure Loss Warning System, Spare Wheel - Space Saver, White exterior colour, Active Light System, Headlight Wash System, Headlights - Adaptive High Beam Assist, Headlights - Bi Xenon, Intelligent Light System, Automatic Climate Control - Two-Zone-Independently Adjustable for Driver and Passenger, Automatically Dimming Rear View Mirror and Folding Exterior Door Mirrors, Partial Electric Front Seats, Roof Lining - Black, Steering Column - Manually Adjustable for Height and Reach, Steering Wheel - Multi-function-12-Button-Controls Audio and Onboard Settings, Trim - Brushed Aluminium, 18in Alloy Wheels - AMG 5 Twin Spoke Design, 18in Alloy Wheels - AMG 7 Spoke Design, AMG bodystyling - front-rear and side skirts, AUX-In Socket and USB Interface in the Centre Armrest, Adaptive Brake System with Hold Function-Hill Start Assist, Agility Control - Sports Suspension with Adaptive Damping System, Airbags - Kneebag, Airbags - Window, Audio 20 Radio CD-6 Speakers-Telephone Keypad-Bluetooth Interface, Centre Armrest - Front, Cup Holder, Door Mirrors - Electrically Adjustable and Heated with LED Indicators, Electric Windows - Front and Rear, Floor Mats - AMG, Headlamp Assist - Automatic Headlamp Activation, Headlights - Bi-Xenon with LED Daytime Running Lights, ISOFIX Child Seat Fixing Points in Rear, Lumbar Support, Power Assisted Steering, Rain Sensing Windscreen Wipers, Seats - Electrically Adjustable Driver and Passenger, Steering Wheel - AMG-Nappa Leather-trimmed and Gear Shift, Storage Package, Tinted, Agility Control Suspension with Adaptive Damping System, Sports Suspension, ABS - Anti-Lock Braking System, ASR - Acceleration Skid Control, Airbags - Dual Stage - Driver, Airbags - Dual Stage - Front Passenger, Airbags - Front Sidebags, Alarm System with Immobiliser and Interior Protection, Automatic Child Seat Recognition Sensor, BAS - Brake Assist, ESP - Electronic Stability Programme, First Aid Kit and Warning Triangle, Hill Start Assist, Pre-Safe Anticipatory Safety System, Remote Central Locking</ExtraFeatures>
    <Reg>WG12 AAE</Reg>
    <Video>https://youtube.com/embed/SknJy1vhakg?autoplay=1andrel=0</Video>
    <MetaTag>Mercedes-Benz C Class 2.1 C250 CDI BlueEfficiency AMG Sport Plus G-Tronic+ Euro 5 (s/s) 4dr Diesel Automatic White</MetaTag>
    <Description>
      Available now is this stunning and well-maintained Mercedes-Benz C-Class C250 CDI BlueEFFICIENCY, a premium executive saloon offering strong diesel performance, luxury comfort, and excellent motorway capability.
      Clearance, external warranty is available.
      ✅ Excellent driving condition.
      ✅ Loads of paperwork.
      ✅ Water pump replaced.
      ✅ Gearbox serviced at around 100k miles.
      ✅ Freshly service.
      ✅ OEM Apple CarPlay unit.
      ✅ Fresh Mot.
      Powered by the 2.1 C250 CDI BlueEFFICIENCY diesel engine paired with a smooth automatic gearbox, it delivers impressive power, outstanding fuel economy, and the refined driving experience Mercedes-Benz is known for.
      ✅ C250 CDI BlueEFFICIENCY • Automatic • Executive Saloon
      Key Features Include:
      • Elegant C-Class styling
      • Full leather interior
      • Heated front seats
      • Satellite navigation system
      • Bluetooth and media connectivity
      • Dual-zone climate control
      • Cruise control
      • Front and rear parking sensors
      • Multifunction steering wheel
      • Alloy wheels
      • Electric windows and mirrors
      • ISOFIX
      Drives superb — powerful, smooth, and extremely refined. No warning lights or mechanical issues.
      • Recently serviced and inspected
      • Ready to drive away today
      ✅ Drive away today – reserve with a refundable £100 deposit (TandCs apply).
      🚚 Nationwide delivery available at competitive rates.
      ⸻
      Why Buy from AW Trade Centre?
      We provide:
      • Full mechanical inspection
      • Free comprehensive warranty
      • HPI clear vehicles (unless otherwise stated)
      • Fresh valet inside and out
      • Friendly, honest, and pressure-free service
      📞 Call or message us today to arrange a viewing or reserve this Mercedes-Benz C250 CDI BlueEFFICIENCY Auto 🚗
    </Description>
    <Image>https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/7421836db9bf483994e5033928d0282e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/7fa60ae8d2204ed5a06c551beb6f9c57.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/7238708bd8d7410d83e37382921ffc45.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/96b3e603733249c9880f0a6811c319fe.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/0042d834fb5147e4a609d5a7a3a49f3b.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/08f02e79addf4270862a3cc5aa0c7698.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/ba5fe941ef824122be6f772325f724aa.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/dd60654d0f1f4a92a9fb395d8ab99bd1.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/08c310d0c7a24e8b9434e75ab3c59975.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/868fe3ca42ea4bd193df1efb51e3e68e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/a074d8c8293e4f2c8cecd8ed36eb19af.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/22ba7d43ac9046b08114f0acbee4f3bf.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/605636d5766a471780d784473b557ee1.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/f8c111c5bd0f46c0872f5445a937a8f6.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/c630e8afebdf42be8d2c3226c9bf0196.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/b9980ad5a1354344acf5288673c578d7.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/be5d3e240a854f9fbeaf297c3b19e661.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/af70461d1b284749b72a413555e6381c.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/a8c16fae3d674d49aa67aa624b3e9715.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/a6464a6b221441e5a54e5ca49c78dc9a.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/bf69f62a989945a7bc8613ddc8ff205b.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/0cd7e1d858e9448dbc7f4144506b85e3.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/64e141646cc04718a98e2c22481122e5.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/3ac44aadfac3485aad82b8e0a44bbcfc.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/a1a3975dd07e4e2bae32725140edb3fa.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/e4a9fa14b617407b9f84444c24b410e4.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/6f4c7adba45b41a7bf8b3de980306b26.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/fe365acb7d7c484da8b23a0b822c4a09.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/e5413b16efe9465a8566be9e7818fcce.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/cba8fbac089a42c1b9f7d39eefd7ad3c.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/72af8553bffa40c693aee001c0d65bbc.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/2bf5e8818a774534a857fa197c489917.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/896bda8be15546fca323f6eb3ae27acf.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/0126265db674417ebeebe3492746e3eb.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/02706a72f5174426881f72750be6df08.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/91dea6f99375476aa7d4ba905ba5cb75.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/6cd38fc058d24edeb2192d3ea73f64fb.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/40c10daea9fc4f22b672390e46be7719.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/abb70e884ce74fd084ae9fd1db4ef0b9.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/b07eb180bc9540ed9bcae60f0f93c4f2.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/f30c54a0db144ef5a2f0d521a6eeb5d4.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/9cf69ef0348940678947aea441e6bc94.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/959d2349d58c446384593bccd65f9c89.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/8cdf167d4b2a4f9da79d365d981d3e90.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/16a33b5bd27442199600a4a180f7c247.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/0a4304f1034c4f5f98f39ded0fbdaeaf.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/d9007ee0ce3d48949dbb01660f61f0e0.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/41a818c4a50240008bb489aa7e585247.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/de4839bd32c24e6aa97085704c03e304.jpg</Image>
    <Tax>200</Tax>
    <Insurance>38E</Insurance>
    <Mpg>54.3</Mpg>
    <AT>https://www.autotrader.co.uk/car-details/202511238086093?journey=DEALER_STOCK_LIST_JOURNEY&amp;sort=price-asc&amp;twcs=true&amp;searchId=a7b1990a-3d0d-4b09-aec4-6595e7680e19&amp;advertising-location=at_profile_cars&amp;advertising-location=at_cars&amp;page=1&amp;postcode=ts233ta&amp;fromsra=&amp;fromDealerSearchResults=&amp;backLinkQueryParams=advertising-location%3Dat_cars%26advertising-location%3Dat_profile_cars%26flrfc%3D1%26onesearchad%3DUsed%26onesearchad%3DNearly%2520New%26onesearchad%3DNew%26postcode%3Dts233ta%26retailerId%3D10041187%26sort%3Dprice-asc&amp;calc-deposit=450&amp;calc-term=48&amp;calc-mileage=10000</AT>
  </Car>
  <Car>
    <ID>10</ID>
    <Name>Vauxhall</Name>
    <Model>Corsa</Model>
    <FullModel>1.4i ecoFLEX Energy Euro 6 5dr (a/c)</FullModel>
    <EyeCatcher>0 OWNERS✅T-CHAIN✅6M WARRANTY✅</EyeCatcher>
    <Value>4999</Value>
    <Mileage>75300</Mileage>
    <YearOfManu>2016</YearOfManu>
    <CatStat>HPI Clear</CatStat>
    <FuelType>Petrol</FuelType>
    <Transmission>Manual</Transmission>
    <Colour>Black</Colour>
    <ExtraFeatures>Bluetooth Connectivity, DAB Digital Radio, Electrical Accessory Socket, Multi Function Display Panel, R4.0 IntelliLink Touch-Screen Infotainment System, City Mode Button - Provides Lighter Steering at Parking Speeds, Cruise Control, Digital Clock with Automatic RDS Time Adjustment, Electronically Controlled Fuel Gauge, Handbrake On Warning Light, Headlight-Brake Light Bulb Failure Warning Light, Key Left in Ignition Audible Warning, Low Fuel Level Warning Light, Rev Counter, Service-Due Indicator, Shift Up Indicator, TPMS - Tyre Pressure Monitoring System, Trip Odometer, 16in Alloy Wheels, Black Foil on B-Pillar, Black exterior colour, Body-Colour Door Handles, Door Mirrors - Body Colour, Electric Windows - Front with Safety Autoreverse and One Touch Facility, Electrically Adjustable-Heated Door Mirrors Wide-Angle on Drivers Side, Electro-Chromatic Anti-Dazzle Drivers Door Mirror, Emergency Spare Steel Wheel, Emergency Tyre Inflation Kit, Fuel Tank Located Ahead of Rear Axle, Heated Rear Window, Heated Windscreen, Intermittent Rear Window Wash-Wipe, Laminated Windscreen, Locking Wheel Bolts for Alloy Wheels, Sight and Light Pack One, Steel Emergency Spare Wheel, Tinted Glass, Automatic Lighting Control, Daytime Running Lights - LED, Door-to-Door Illumination, Electric Headlight Beam Levelling, Front Fog Lights with Black Surround, Halogen Headlights, High-Level LED Centre Rear Brake Light, Lights On Audible Warning, Adjustable Rear Seat Backrest, Air Blend Heater with Four Speed Fan and Illuminated Controls, Air Conditioning includes Air Recirculation Facility, Anti-Submarining Ramps in Seats, Black cloth interior, Chrome Effect Gear Knob Trim, Chrome Effect Handbrake Button, Chrome Effect Interior Door Handles, Dipping Rear-View Mirror, Drinks Holder in Centre Console, Driver Information Centre - White Graphics on Black Background, Drivers and Front Passengers Tiltable Assist Handles, Electrically Heated Front Seats, Front Door Pockets, Glovebox with Lid, Head Restraints - Height Adjustable Outer Rear Seats, Height-Adjustable Front Seat Head Restraints, Illuminated Luggage Area, Instrument Panel Light Dimmer, Interior Pollen Filter, Interior Tailgate Handle, Load Restraint Lashing Eyes, Luggage Compartment Cover, Map Reading Lights, One-Piece Folding Rear Seat, Rain Sensitive Windscreen Wipers, Rear Door Pockets, Rear Reading Lights, Reclining Front Seats, Rhutenium Facia with Chrome-Effect Inserts, Seats - Drivers Height Adjustment, Side Window Demist Vents and Four Adjustable Heating and Ventilation Outputs, Steering Column - Adjustable for Reach and Rake, Steering Wheel - Mounted Audio Controls, Stowage Facility for Luggage Compartment Cover Behind Rear Seats, Sunvisor - Passenger with Vanity Mirrors and Cover, Twin Sunvisors - Drivers with Vanity Mirror and Cover, Two Rear Passengers Tiltable Assist Handles, Two Speed Windscreen Wipers with Variable Intermittent Wipe, Welcome Lighting, Winter Pack, Speed Sensitive Power Assisted Steering, Adaptive Brake Lights, Adjustable Speed Limit Audible Warning, Airbags - Front Seat Side-Impact, Anti-lock Braking System - ABS with Electronic Brakeforce Distribution, CBC - Cornering Brake Control, Child Proof Locks on Rear Doors, Deactivation Switch for Front Passengers Airbag, Drag Torque Control, Driver and Passenger Seatbelt Force Limiters, Drivers Dual-Stage Airbag, EBA - Emergency Brake Assist, ESP - Electronic Stability Programme Plus with Traction Control, Electronic Engine Deadlock Immobiliser, Electronic Theft Protection For Audio Equipment, Folding Key, Front Anti-Roll Bar, Front Passengers Dual-Stage Airbags, Front Seatbelt Pretensioner System, Full Length Curtain Airbags, HSA - Hill Start Assist, Height Adjustable Front Seatbelts, ISOFIX Child Seat Restraint System for Outer Rear Seats Incorporating Top Tether, Pedal Release System, Rear Fog Lights, Reinforced Passenger Safety Cell, Remote Control Central Locking with Security Deadlocks, Seatbelt Unfastened Audible Warning For All Seats, Side Impact Protection Beams, Straight Line Stability Control, Three Inertia-Reel Lap and Diagonal Rear Seatbelts, VIN - Visible Vehicle Identification Number</ExtraFeatures>
    <Reg>VO66 UAE</Reg>
    <Video></Video>
    <MetaTag>Vauxhall Corsa 1.4i ecoFLEX Energy Euro 6 5dr (a/c) Petrol Manual Black</MetaTag>
    <Description>
      Available now is this well-presented and economical 2016 (66) Vauxhall Corsa 1.4i ecoFLEX Energy, a practical hatchback offering low running costs, great comfort, and excellent everyday usability.
      Powered by the reliable 1.4 petrol ecoFLEX engine, it’s smooth, efficient, and ULEZ compliant, making it ideal for new drivers, commuting, or city driving.
      This example also benefits from having the timing chain recently replaced, giving added peace of mind for the next owner.
      ✅ ULEZ compliant • Low insurance • Cheap to run
      ✅ Timing chain replaced
      Key Features Include:
      • Apple CarPlay
      • Android Auto
      • Touchscreen infotainment system
      • Bluetooth and media connectivity
      • Cruise control
      • Air conditioning
      • Heated seats (Energy trim feature)
      • Heated steering wheel
      • Multifunction steering wheel
      • Electric windows and mirrors
      • Alloy wheels
      • ISOFIX
      • Daytime running lights
      Drives great — smooth, quiet, and economical. No warning lights or mechanical issues.
      • Recently serviced and inspected
      • MOT expires 30/01/2027
      ✅ Drive away today – reserve VO66 UAE with a refundable £100 deposit (TandCs apply).
      🚚 Nationwide delivery available at competitive rates.
      ⸻
      Why Buy from AW Trade Centre?
      We provide:
      • Full mechanical inspection
      • Free comprehensive warranty
      • HPI clear vehicles (unless otherwise stated)
      • Fresh valet inside and out
      • Friendly, honest, and pressure-free service
      📞 Call or message us today to arrange a viewing or reserve this Vauxhall Corsa 1.4 ecoFLEX Energy.
    </Description>
    <Image>https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/d2c528a46f4743b19515d577d845f283.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/c6377346a85b4d7c8722b548e817f75d.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/308c5ba434384a7991dca043baef5a1a.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/f57b2c9438d84c8a9de0920b4cfefa22.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/2c0f5e26d2264c3f87c27acbd23a9255.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/da1aa44c2a934e41a2f01b1b82efe11b.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/150c2de2fb8441d29bb255d8625970fd.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/29ec9296e2124834a5e572d72d73ae8c.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/0150930aa3904b67897e51e272118687.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/abb879880de74ed3aac5ed7fc33ae7c6.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/bb0bff42a6f342ca80a6598c701e034a.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/5d67d44f697e49a9b65b2915feb74530.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/5f8ce5afd5234fd58be5d6f8fa82ce72.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/b3ce57c1f85740e298d6e2280a9513b1.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/25fb251da4514993aadfd54b1cc2cd37.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/887819c2d85e432c881330ac215673ce.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/7ef6dc64c37742df833dea63b0d97738.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/d883087f83ad4ee79dcc4ed6e3d568e9.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/95faae5528b94fabb72171fe7141a9fd.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/5800035c487a42458cc32019b5b05109.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/4e97a7e8340943ceb11224b145d95654.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/c82761a11cae4118b8f9fcbe862bb5da.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/23b3605a5d504616b1731eb3f487de52.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/b1fda95b45f148d2af2ac4b608ee84d3.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/bad1cddd19ee40b598527042f5a6e39e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/a115c3e95133437bbe1fcbf2efba4c6b.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/738d9c77c6ea405282bc3fd011e89e96.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/cb3e96bdf8cb4a55a03bde29b613941a.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/6043b04e63ea430f8deab3244d05f5fa.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/e93345d54e134f02baaa584757ee211f.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/197a1c7fc84b442f99d7338aa9229132.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/cf0a2d9a54ed467db27dabb329662ede.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/e1bf9d97ea584c07bc8f3a1af95d8b06.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/d5b2871d2173442581aaa99547ccc87d.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/c47e7ca7f5ee440f96d55e1b3e9901ef.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/316450eb15da455199983aa46022a499.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/28877beacc244877a4bf1e2d2a1cd4e0.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/10ef54c3c4e44830a71141c9d1352316.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/0f58b7f899a84f03b0f90b06da88045c.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/edf1a9215a5248abaea48c8bab09b929.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/59dab1378e6e4afc94b47faf2c96af30.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/0383b02e086c45f3a6721fed33436ab7.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/93887abfa5324544bd2e3fdfc0336077.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/7abaf20e05254979b38a54f54c95f2b2.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/2f230c9a334041cc9015b9820fd3b084.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/fa97525e46ef40b68c4335cf1c76ec1b.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/cff28ad3c3b34a78b856b54f41ec4e25.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/a04917bbc7b6419a8bf50b06bf5079f6.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/e8c060584b7b45ea9431766cad46a2c3.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/4be659c3953640a0b1ef33e520283dc5.jpg</Image>
    <Tax>35</Tax>
    <Insurance>03E</Insurance>
    <Mpg>55.4</Mpg>
    <AT>https://www.autotrader.co.uk/car-details/202603110611615?journey=DEALER_STOCK_LIST_JOURNEY&amp;sort=price-asc&amp;twcs=true&amp;searchId=a7b1990a-3d0d-4b09-aec4-6595e7680e19&amp;advertising-location=at_profile_cars&amp;advertising-location=at_cars&amp;page=1&amp;postcode=ts233ta&amp;fromsra=&amp;fromDealerSearchResults=&amp;backLinkQueryParams=advertising-location%3Dat_cars%26advertising-location%3Dat_profile_cars%26flrfc%3D1%26onesearchad%3DUsed%26onesearchad%3DNearly%2520New%26onesearchad%3DNew%26postcode%3Dts233ta%26retailerId%3D10041187%26sort%3Dprice-asc&amp;calc-deposit=500&amp;calc-term=48&amp;calc-mileage=10000&amp;calc-selected-product=HP</AT>
  </Car>
  <Car>
    <ID>11</ID>
    <Name>Volvo</Name>
    <Model>V40</Model>
    <FullModel>1.6 D2 R-Design Nav Euro 5 (s/s) 5dr</FullModel>
    <EyeCatcher>£20 R’TAX✅6M WARRANTY✅2 OWNERS</EyeCatcher>
    <Value>5450</Value>
    <Mileage>90400</Mileage>
    <YearOfManu>2014</YearOfManu>
    <CatStat>HPI Clear</CatStat>
    <FuelType>Diesel</FuelType>
    <Transmission>Manual</Transmission>
    <Colour>Black</Colour>
    <ExtraFeatures>12V Socket - Front, 12V Socket - Rear, Amplifier 45W x4, Annual Map Updates x2, Bluetooth Handsfree System, Colour Display Screen - 7in, DAB - Digital Audio Broadcasting Radio, DVD Player, European Mapping, RDS-TMC - Traffic Message Channel, Radio/CD, Remote Control for Digital TV with Integrated Satellite Navigation and Multimedia System, Satellite Navigation - inc RDS/TMC and European Mapping (DVD), Sensus Connect with Premium Sound by Harman Kardon, Speakers x8, USB/iPod Input, 8in Active TFT Crystal Drivers Instrument Display, Cruise Control, IDIS - Intelligent Driver Information System, Information Centre, Voice Activated Control, 17in Alloy Wheels - Ixion Matt Black, Black exterior colour, Chrome Window Trim, Door Mirrors - Power Folding with Ground Lights, Door Mirrors - Silver Matt (R-Design), Electric Windows - Auto Open and Close, Electric Windows - Front and Rear, Exhaust Pipes - Twin (R-Design), Locking Wheel Nuts, Roof Spoiler, Side Marker Illumination, Tyre Sealant Kit and Compressor, Unique R-Design Lower Front Nose, Headlights - Levelling System, Headlights - Tunnel Sensor, High Level LED Brake Light, Home Safe and Approach Lighting, LED Day Running Lights, A-Pillar Parking Ticket Holder, Armrest - Front/Sliding, Armrest - Rear Centre, Black part leather interior, Charcoal Headlining, Climate Control - Electronic, Cupholders - Rear, Floor Mats - Sports (R-Design), Front Reading - Footwell and Theatre Lights, Front Storage Box with Cupholders, Glovebox - Cooled, Height and Reach Adjustable Steering Column, Illuminated Driver and Passenger Vanity Mirrors, Illuminated Gear Knob, Instrument Cluster - Blue Dials (R-Design), Pollen Filter, R-Design Aluminium Trim, R-Design Nubuck Sports - Charcoal, Seats - Front Lumbar Support, Sports Pedals - Aluminium (R-Design), Steering Wheel - Leather/Sports (R-Design) with Logo, Steering Wheel Remote Audio Controls, Versatile Split Folding Rear Seats - 60-40, Dynamic Chassis, Power Steering System, Speed Limiter, ABS - Anti-Lock Brake System, Adaptive Brake Lights, Advanced Stability Control and Torque Vectoring, Airbags - Drivers Dual Stage, Airbags - Dual Chamber SIPS, Airbags - Passenger Dual Stage, Anti-Theft Alarm, Central Locking - Remote, City Safety, Deadlock System, Driver Knee Airbag, Dynamic Stability Control, EBA - Emergency Brake Assistance, IC - Inflatable Curtains, ISOFIX Child Seat Preparation - Rear, Immobiliser, Level Sensor, Passenger Airbag Cut-Off Switch, Pedestrian Airbag Technology, SIPS - Side Impact Protection System, Traction Control, Visible VIN Plate, Volume Sensor, WHIPS - Whiplash Protection System - Front Seats, Warning Triangle</ExtraFeatures>
    <Reg>NG64 HHD</Reg>
    <Video></Video>
    <MetaTag>Volvo V40 1.6 D2 R-Design Nav Euro 5 (s/s) 5dr Diesel Manual Black</MetaTag>
    <Description>
      Available now is this stylish and well-maintained 2015 (64) Volvo V40 1.6 D2 R-Design Nav, a premium hatchback offering sporty styling, excellent fuel economy, and Volvo’s renowned comfort and safety.
      Powered by the efficient 1.6 D2 diesel engine, it delivers outstanding MPG and a smooth, refined drive — ideal for commuting, motorway driving, or everyday use.
      ✅ £20 road tax • R-Design Styling • Excellent MPG • Premium Hatchback
      Key Features Include:
      • R-Design styling package
      • Satellite navigation system
      • Touchscreen infotainment system
      • Bluetooth and media connectivity
      • Cruise control
      • Dual-zone climate control
      • Sports seats
      • Alloy wheels
      • Multifunction steering wheel
      • Electric windows and mirrors
      • ISOFIX
      • Daytime running lights
      Drives superb — smooth, comfortable, and very economical. No warning lights or mechanical issues.
      • Recently serviced and inspected
      • MOT expires 25/02/2027
      ✅ Drive away today – reserve NG64 HHD with a refundable £100 deposit (TandCs apply).
      🚚 Nationwide delivery available at competitive rates.
      ⸻
      Why Buy from AW Trade Centre?
      We provide:
      • Full mechanical inspection
      • Free comprehensive warranty
      • HPI clear vehicles (unless otherwise stated)
      • Fresh valet inside and out
      • Friendly, honest, and pressure-free service
      📞 Call or message us today to arrange a viewing or reserve this Volvo V40 D2 R-Design Nav.
    </Description>
    <Image>https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/e67cd120265c4326a24fdb4381564ef8.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/911a10ef3d834b5bbb700ac75d77b952.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/27d3c7c3db9441dcad526b28f73ba8bd.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/a773d303c2a949da92853c086374344a.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/4fcf4536ff464fdeb3af24e18b6b1698.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/7fa20f230c1246ecac6e5a174620911a.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/1ed045909bfc4a4b92408468bee08134.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/3fada490b8b2495ab918d8faadba55d5.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/36d3e6991d6c4d2f98a1aef4e0ecd3df.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/ee1e8fb1a2fe4607b27f8cff43898e9e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/66aee42191f44028b2b29aa110e4a5fc.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/c1a8c35fc29c4d64bee7e3dd8d2a28a8.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/c241d3eacb3c4eb188b818f05072efa4.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/03e7820997184114acbaef485b8b12e8.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/98b07f66e342447fa1e73e9c04146dba.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/d59b33be02c54806b75a9f56c9cc9d5e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/ede7d10a391b46f6aea2e8e87d09230a.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/8a928b6874304f72813044b8b9f46b52.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/e68caeadb42f402e9d418e0f235ec0ea.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/2995b7a927064ce887e5f987cd394962.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/ec59a847281841309ece297bee829be2.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/1d4e4b1e544c44a5a63ef733e7670273.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/c6246ecbd7ba4252b0d25c41857d095f.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/83fde5975b2c4182b0392c750904c961.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/5de183592e9f4922920d08c702378b7c.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/1a42201580c843a1982b38f9da44a335.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/7fa93c39d6254312b033787f964f6150.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/a3aa407ab90d43bbbf946bd2f3fab70c.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/dbe4f5ca006441fca23a681ecb709495.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/6c7bf5e26e93426ba2939e5fa38e4b0c.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/1667d308caaa4771baaa9b55fc0b7a75.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/5ffbc132547a475da8cf3719f6dfa3bd.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/ac6feaa7577d41559bcd046f81cf198f.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/61ca1b00ad5e475db595906df38c8234.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/588b53e6c8b342299e48474e0309c732.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/c6cba59982294ea6bd2bd5bbe18ec853.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/0216aae7943f42d9a1f5daf2be3c4628.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/5b403b2871994552b7d4c37914e3a50b.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/fdfcf9ad52984384bb0261f517d89eb1.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/2e8729f9bb4f419ca43d3f4a05354a4e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/4c4b5bdacc8c4329a68e25b0ac52e116.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/f12beb81810d4bcabba33b205f4d1377.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/dd55df683ff34fdbbe00d8f7fe9a618c.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/31a9ffc1d64b4854b3b21100430fe433.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/10b87c4e92ce409fbe8645b89cea52c8.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/044695b53a804a8c86f0769c3ded0fbf.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/f8fd387392c64a7586a0779c20e406c7.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/131058d3da5a4900bf10dcd1d5cadb1e.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/6e2b5e1612d34b4eaf161528b863141b.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/4f53872283ad461cb1e4a168acb73c27.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/fcc6ee9dfb514838b6f8c4d8ef841409.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/71046058454f42489f9138f2052347a6.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/8c9701c69a834cf5a1fba570f221d520.jpg,https://m.atcdn.co.uk/a/media/{resize}/7f32b64ce3a04849974ce1dbc5075577.jpg</Image>
    <Tax>20</Tax>
    <Insurance>17E</Insurance>
    <Mpg>83.1</Mpg>
    <AT>https://www.autotrader.co.uk/car-details/202603311166018?journey=DEALER_STOCK_LIST_JOURNEY&amp;sort=price-asc&amp;twcs=true&amp;searchId=a7b1990a-3d0d-4b09-aec4-6595e7680e19&amp;advertising-location=at_profile_cars&amp;advertising-location=at_cars&amp;page=1&amp;postcode=ts233ta&amp;fromsra=&amp;fromDealerSearchResults=&amp;backLinkQueryParams=advertising-location%3Dat_cars%26advertising-location%3Dat_profile_cars%26flrfc%3D1%26onesearchad%3DUsed%26onesearchad%3DNearly%2520New%26onesearchad%3DNew%26postcode%3Dts233ta%26retailerId%3D10041187%26sort%3Dprice-asc&amp;calc-deposit=545&amp;calc-term=48&amp;calc-mileage=10000</AT>
  </Car>
</Cars>
